<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1">
<script async="false" type="text/javascript" src="chrome-extension://fnjhmkhhmkbjkkabndcnnogagogbneec/in-page.js"/>


<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Naples%20Botanical%20Garden?-Naples-Attractions-1-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/13/5a/09/d4/view-to-gardens.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Naples Botanical Garden is a 170-acre world-class garden paradise that features the plants and cultures of the tropics and subtropics between the latitudes of 26 degrees North and 26 degrees South including Brazil, the Caribbean, Southeast Asia, and Florida. The Garden also offers 90 acres of beautifully restored natural habitats and walking trails offer educational entertainment and enjoyment for people of all ages.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Naples%20Pier?-Naples-Attractions-2-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/03/9d/bd/f2/naples-pier.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Naples Pier is a favorite location for sightseers. The Pier features restrooms, showers, ADA beach access mat, and a concession stand with covered eating area and beach supplies.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Lowdermilk%20Beach?-Naples-Attractions-3-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0e/b2/9a/af/lowdermilk-beach.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Lowdermilk Park is one of Naples' premier beachfront parks. The park has parking spaces, a concession stand, sand volleyball courts, two children's playgrounds, picnic tables, benches, restroom and shower facilities, two gazebos for rent, and ADA beach access mats.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Revs%20Institute?-Naples-Attractions-4-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/15/a2/ec/a5/revs-institute.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Revs Institute® will reopen on Tuesday, September 13th. Tickets must be purchased online for specific dates/times in advance. No telephone orders or walk-up visitors can be accommodated. Revs Institute is dedicated to the study of the automobile past, present and future. Revs Institute offers visitors an exceptional opportunity to view over 100 of the most influential automobiles of our time. Many of the cars are unique or exceptionally rare, and each meets rigid standards of historical, technical, aesthetic or social significance. To enhance the visitor experience, specially designed interactive displays and artifact showcases are presented within four themed galleries. They include unique items from the extensive Revs Institute library and archives. Revs Institute is a not-for-profit 501(c)(3) organization.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Naples%20Zoo%20at%20Caribbean%20Gardens?-Naples-Attractions-5-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1c/a8/38/74/masamba-the-male-african.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>This historic tropical garden and nationally accredited zoo features wildlife experiences to inspire people of all ages to respect, value and help conserve wildlife and our natural world. Visit today to enjoy your favorite animals like lions, monkeys, and giraffes. Ask those questions you've always wondered about at the Meet the Keeper Series. Be fascinated by rare creatures during premier wildlife shows. Cruise through islands of monkeys, lemurs, and gibbons. Watch our professional staff hand-feed American alligators while dispelling popular myths. The zoo is nationally accredited by the Association of Zoos and Aquariums, the organization that sets the highest standards for wildlife care, education, and conservation.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Clam%20Pass%20Park?-Naples-Attractions-6-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0b/a9/09/73/view-of-the-gulf-form.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Clam Pass Park is a beautiful beach access point in one of the most highly populated areas of Collier County, Florida. Clam Pass Park has 171 public parking spaces since it is also one of the most popular beach access points, rivaling Vanderbilt Beach.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Third%20Street%20South?-Naples-Attractions-8-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/10/82/6a/d1/third-street-south-is.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Just blocks from Naples Pier and Gulf beaches, THIRD STREET SOUTH is an abundantly landscaped, historic neighborhood known for its chic shops and wide variety of restaurants and cafés where excellent food, superb wines and the glorious option of outdoor dining make every meal memorable. Start your weekend's activities by visiting Naples' original Farmer's Market which takes place behind Tommy Bahamas from 7:30am - 11:30am every Saturday morning throughout the year. Discover everything from fish, meats, pasta, and cheese, to breads, produce, fresh ground coffee beans, and the best people and dog watching in town. Come for the day, come for the night, but don't miss the unique glamour and good times to be found on Third Street South.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Conservancy%20of%20Southwest%20Florida?-Naples-Attractions-9-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/02/50/a8/b9/new-filter-marsh-and.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>At the Conservancy of Southwest Florida, we believe the more we can connect people with nature, the more willing they are to protect it. And our Nature Center helps us to do just that! At the Nature Center, guests get connected to conservation through hands-on interactive experiences in the Dalton Discover Center, on our famous electric boat tours and in our Little Explorer Play Zone. The Conservancy Nature Center is also listed as Site #69 on the Great Florida Birding Trail. Here you will learn about the importance of our resources, understand the role the Conservancy of Southwest Florida plays in protecting those treasures and get inspired to take action to help protect our water, land, wildlife and future.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Tin%20City?-Naples-Attractions-10-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/17/a6/d4/2f/tin-city.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Tin City Waterfront Marketplace in Historic downtown Naples, FL is the original shopping sensation and home to three unique buildings with a waterfront boardwalk full of activity, more then 30 charming boutiques, 2 waterfront restaurants and a variety of water adventures including daily sightseeing cruises, fishing charters, jet boat thrill rides and more!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Naples%20Depot%20Museum?-Naples-Attractions-12-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/02/d0/41/cc/naples-depot-museum.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Long hidden on the fringe of Florida's Gulf coast and overlooked by developers until well into the 1880s, Naples' catalyst for settlement finally arrived forty years later when two rival railroads rolled into town within ten days of each other. Set in Naples' restored Seaboard Air Line Railway passenger station, the Naples Depot Museum welcomes visitors back to the railroading boom days of the Roaring Twenties and explains how generations of Southwest Floridians used technology and transportation to conquer a vast and seemingly impenetrable frontier.Seminole dugout canoes, a mule wagon, antique swamp buggy, restored rail cars and exciting interactive exhibits tell the story of how trade and travel transformed Naples from a napping village of 300 souls into today's glittering Gulf coast resort. The Naples Depot Museum is listed on the National Register of Historic Places and is conveniently located in downtown Naples.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Freedom%20Park?-Naples-Attractions-13-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0c/1e/f5/99/photo5jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A wooden boardwalk meanders around 50 acres of restored wetlands, lakes  viewing platforms.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Village%20Shops%20on%20Venetian%20Bay?-Naples-Attractions-14-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/1c/10/dc/5a/the-village-shops-on.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The beautiful waterfront setting, colorful Mediterranean architecture, art sculptures, boutique shops and established restaurants, make the Village on Venetian Bay one of the most notable landmarks and attractions in Naples for more than twenty years. Discover apparel for the whole family from name brand merchandise to sophisticated private label collections. There are art galleries, gifts for the home, exquisite timepieces, and dazzling jewelry to define your style. Need a bite to eat? The Village has a range of restaurants with indoor and outdoor waterfront settings that range from fine dining to casual Pub-grub—the perfect way to satisfy your appetite and take in the sights over Venetian Bay.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Holocaust%20Museum%20%20Cohen%20Education%20Center?-Naples-Attractions-15-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/21/85/28/visitors-on-a-docent.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>COVID-19 Update: Pre-purchase of Timed-entry Admission tickets required prior to visit – tickets available at www.HMCEC.org. Capacity is limited and health  safety measures include social distancing, sanitizing frequently touched surfaces, hand-sanitizing stations and mask requirement to protect Guests, Volunteers and Staff members; Collier County “Paradise Pledge” program partner. Hours of Operation: 1:00pm-4:00pm Wednesday, Thursday, Saturday, and Sunday, with last entry at 3:00pm. Self-guided audio tours available for smartphone and tablets – earbuds required. Docent on duty to answer questions. For more information on new visitor procedures, current exhibits and upcoming virtual events and programs, visit HMCEC.org. The Museum was inspired by a local middle school project on the Holocaust. Its mission is “to teach the lessons of the Holocaust to inspire action against bigotry, hatred and violence.” New larger location incudes updated exhibits and expanded parking.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Gordon%20River%20Greenway?-Naples-Attractions-17-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/06/ef/06/60/walkway.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Gordon River Greenway is a nearly 2-mile system of trails and boardwalks running along the Gordon River.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Collier%20Museum%20at%20Government%20Center?-Naples-Attractions-19-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/d0/48/09/collier-county-museum.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Nestled on five acres of native Florida landscaping, our flagship museum at the County Government center in Naples offers newly created exhibits and galleries that capture the full panorama of local history. Pack a picnic and linger a while in the museum's shady backyard. Then do a little exploring on your own in our native gardens, restored Naples cottages, the archaeology lab, Seminole village or Calusa Indian camp. Enlarged twice, the museum's main gallery offers over 10,000 square feet of new displays, plus a traveling exhibit room, lecture hall, and gift shop.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Naples%20Museum%20Of%20Military%20History?-Naples-Attractions-20-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/17/87/1a/e3/the-main-room-of-the.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Southwest Florida Military Museum. They have thousands of Military artifacts from all branches of the Military. The Museum is located at the Naples Municipal Airport which was originally built by the Army Corps of Engineers to train pilots for the Pacific theater in WWII. They have now opened the 2nd room we call the Annex, that has everything else not connected to WWII and the Naples Airport Vietnam-Korea Middle East wars and some left over WWII articles. What has begun as a Museum Honoring Military Aviation in World War 2, has evolved into so much more. You can now see historical artifacts dating back to the Revolutionary War and all the way up to the present day Iraq  Afghanistan conflicts.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Naples%20Preserve?-Naples-Attractions-21-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/06/25/15/f5/the-naples-preserve.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Known for gopher tortoises, this environmental reserve has a wooden walkway for human visitors.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Naples%20Players%20at%20the%20Sugden%20Community%20Theatre%20?-Naples-Attractions-22-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/09/1b/4e/3c/the-naples-players.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Naples Players enriches, educates, and entertains our community through a superior theatre experience. TNP will always provide a quality collaborative and creative experience for volunteers, staff, and audiences.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Third%20Street%20South%20Farmers%20Market?-Naples-Attractions-23-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/10/80/3f/c7/fresh-tomatoes.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Year-round, the Third Street Farmer’s Market is open every Saturday morning from 7:30 until 11:30 a.m. The Market overflows with fresh produce, flowers, pastas, cheeses, seafood, grass-fed beef, pastries  baked goods, prepared foods, jams, relishes, fresh roasted coffee beans and much more. Music, coffee, dog treats, and many other delights make the Third Street Farmer’s Market perfect for grown-ups, children, dogs, and every other member of the family.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/KAJ%20Gallery?-Naples-Attractions-24-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/15/b7/78/8c/kaj-gallery.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>KAJ Gallery is a contemporary art gallery located in the heart of the Design District in Naples, Florida. The gallery was opened by longtime friends Jason Taylor and sculptor Kosmas Ballis in November 2018. Their goal with a full-fledged art gallery was so they could expand and diversify their offerings to collectors and art lovers alike.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Coastland%20Center?-Naples-Attractions-26-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0c/7b/fb/07/ta-img-20160811-171411.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Shopping mall, opened in 1976. It features Macy's, JCPenney, and Dillard's as its anchors. It hosts a food court and many other specialty stores.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Ankrolab%20Brewing%20Company?-Naples-Attractions-30-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1a/79/82/d8/front-of-ankrolab-brewing.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Ankrolab Brewing Company is passionate about bringing our patrons the finest beer we can produce. That passion begins with beer’s most important ingredient- water. We utilize the newest technology of reverse osmosis (the RO in Ankrolab) to strip our source water of everything. Yes. Everything. A blank page. Our starting water is in fact so pure that we must reintroduce minerals before it is usable. Although this technique is costly and takes extra time, we feel it is a requirement in making our beer the best it can be. This means that if you are drinking a Belgian Quadruple, we are recreating the water profile of the town in which that style was created. Come join us for a taste of beer's history, present and future trends. There is ample seating both inside and out on the dog friendly beer garden. We have shuffleboard, corn hole and many board games available to enjoy. There are different food trucks onsite daily and you are always welcome to bring food or order in.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Arthur%20L.%20Allen%20Tennis%20Center?-Naples-Attractions-31-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0e/22/77/8b/great-tennis-club-house.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Award winning public tennis center in the heart of Old Naples. The tennis center has 12 state of the art Hydro-Grid lighted Har-Tru (clay-like surface) courts. We offer everything from adult group clinics, league play, private lessons, social round robins, junior programming and social play.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Naples%20Art?-Naples-Attractions-32-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/23/d1/ce/f5/outdoor-art-show.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Naples Art is a respected and award-winning non-profit organization that has served and enriched the community by championing education, interest, and involvement in the visual arts in Southwest Florida since its inception in 1954. Naples Art serves as a catalyst for individual artists of all ages and skill levels and continues to inspire all who visit to live and think artistically. A working art center, it creates unique opportunities for local artists and guests as well with a full calendar of events each season.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Naples%20Regional%20Library?-Naples-Attractions-33-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0b/5f/04/1b/patio-entrance-to-the.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Public library.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/East%20Naples%20Community%20Park?-Naples-Attractions-34-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1a/79/bb/12/30-courts.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Community recreation spot with soccer fields, basketball  tennis courts, plus a play area  a pond.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Naples%20Train%20Museum?-Naples-Attractions-38-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/14/f8/79/52/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>See yourself in a miniature drive-in movie theater. See Thomas the Tank Engine run amongst interactive circus and park accessories. At any given time there are 9 trains operating simultaneously on the layout.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Opera%20Naples?-Naples-Attractions-39-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/11/34/c2/8e/madama-butterfly-november.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located in the heart of Naples in Southwest Florida’s Collier County, Opera Naples is dedicated to presenting opera productions and concerts of the highest quality. An artistic powerhouse in an area known for its pristine beaches world class dining, shopping, and art galleries, Opera Naples is a cultural gem in Southwest Florida. Each season, Opera Naples produces classic grand operas at Artis-Naples, as well as chamber opera and concerts at the David and Cecile Wang Opera Center. A staunch proponent of community service and educational outreach, the company has introduced opera to over 60,000 local area children since its inception and offers various programs, through in local schools, the Resident Artists Program and Summer Youth Program. Over the past decade, the company has earned local, regional and state government support. Opera Naples is grateful to its sponsors, patrons and many supporters who have helped it become an important part of the cultural fabric of the region.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Tin%20City%20Waterfront%20Shops?-Naples-Attractions-48-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/1b/b6/02/frieds-learning-about.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Tin City is a specialty shopping district. It is open-air, specializing in antiques and local handmade novelties. There are four separate buildings. You can buy food, antiques, clothes, seashells, candles, wine, mood rings, and much more.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Naples%20Backyard%20History's%20Heritage%20Trail%20Museum?-Naples-Attractions-49-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/02/66/74/87/nbh-old-naples-museum.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Naples Backyard History Old Naples Museum showcases the history of the Tamiami Trail and the Big Cypress Preserve in the Everglades. Enjoy the aerial photography exhibit of "Naples Then and Now" telling the history of Naples from it's beginnings and the developemnet over the years to present day. Rediscover the Ancient Indian Canal short cut from the Bay to the Ocean. Authentic Seminole clothing displayed as well. Admission is free but donations are always welcomed and appreciated.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Lux%20VIP%20Transportation?-Naples-Attractions-80-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/19/7d/63/6d/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Lux VIP service is one of the top-notch transportation service providers in the World. Headquartered in Naples,Florida, our goal is to offer impeccable chauffeur Services around South West Florida and surrounding areas. Lux VIP’s mission is to provide the safest and most reliable transportation service. We offer luxurious limousine services for every event and occasion in SWFL.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Art%20On%20Fifth%20Ave%20Naples?-Naples-Attractions-82-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/24/f7/c4/ff/christine-fifer.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A fine art gallery showing works of art created by local and international artists that are collected all over the world.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Beautiful%20Health?-Naples-Attractions-86-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1b/e3/49/88/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Green clean beauty and health boutique. Our spa services include facials, micro needling, and massage therapy. We have carefully selected the most nourishing products for your hair, skin and wellbeing. </image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Coco%20Art%20Gallery%20Naples?-Naples-Attractions-87-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/24/51/ec/7c/welcome-to-the-gallery.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located at the Coastland Center in Naples, Florida near Macy's, the COCO Art Gallery is a nonprofit cooperative operated by the Art Council of Southwest Florida. It is a year-round venue for exhibiting and selling the original work of the talented artists who are members of the Art Council's 21 affiliate organizations. Generally you will find that the gallery has 40 to 50 local artists' work on display and it refreshes about half of the inventory the second Monday of every month. ​ Participating artists offer oil, pastel, acrylic and watercolor paintings, photography, ceramics, glass, textiles, jewelry, wood, statues, seasonal cards fiber art and more. PLEASE NOTE THAT THE GALLERY IS CLOSED THE 2ND TUESDAY OF EACH MONTH FOR INVENTORY PURPOSES</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Prime%20Limo%20Naples?-Naples-Attractions-93-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/18/fa/b3/6f/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Whether you’re flying for business or pleasure, getting to the airport on time is essential to make your journey a successful one. Prime Limo Naples is focused on the customer experience. From pickup to drop-off we aim to provide an exceptional transportation experience.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Patty's%20Apparel?-Naples-Attractions-109-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/1c/85/dd/3f/patty-s-apparel.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Patty's Apparel, in Naples, FL, is the leading women's clothing store serving Collier and Lee counties since 2002. We specialize in women's clothing, free alterations, complimentary gift wrapping, special orders, free delivery, and much more. For your next clothing purchase, contact Patty's Apparel in Naples today!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Art2d%20Gallery?-Naples-Attractions-110-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1c/5b/ec/42/art-gallery-naples-fl.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Contemporary Art Gallery in Naples Florida featuring the paintings of local artist Timothy Parker. Large abstract paintings, Tropical bird artwork, Contemporary landscapes, Modern seascapes, Figurative Art and Wall sculptures. Large originals to small abstract paintings as well as fine art prints.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Quidley%20%20Company?-Naples-Attractions-114-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1a/cc/b6/ea/getlstd-property-photo.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>When visiting the galleries of Quidley  Company you will find exceptional paintings by today’s finest contemporary and traditional artists. Committed to building collections of distinction, Quidley  Company works with integrity, transparency, and discretion to fulfill clients’ needs and visions, and offers a full range of art-related services.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Marine%20Arts%20Gallery?-Naples-Attractions-115-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/15/be/36/c1/getlstd-property-photo.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Marine Arts Gallery has been a family run art gallery since 1968 with a large selection of fine art.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Gardner%20Colby%20Gallery?-Naples-Attractions-116-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/14/c1/31/86/gallery-exterior-386.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>One of Florida's most respected fine art galleries, Gardner Colby Galleries are located on "Gallery Row" in the heart of Old Naples' elegant Third Street South shopping district. Established in 1994, the gallery represents an exceptional group of contemporary American artists, and features an eclectic collection of paintings, sculpture and glass.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/East%20West%20Fine%20Art?-Naples-Attractions-118-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0d/d8/50/a6/mikhail-shapovalenko.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>After nearly 20 years in business, Gallery on Fifth is now East West Fine Art (EWFA), with two locations in Naples.9115 Strada Place in Mercato shopping center, and 2425 Tamiami Tr. N. in the Bigham Jewelers building. Recognized for its contributions to economic and cultural development by the Collier County Government, EWFA's mission is to bring work by academically trained, world renowned Russian, American and European.artists to Naples.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Marianne%20Friedland%20Gallery?-Naples-Attractions-120-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0e/45/a4/f8/wolf-kahn-paintings-and.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The gallery specializes in modern and contemporary works of art by such noted artists as Wolf Kahn, Milton Avery, Al Held, Esteban Vicente, Janet Fish, Hans Hofmann and Master American Printmakers.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Mediterrano?-Naples-Restaurants-1-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/12/aa/e9/mediterrano.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Welcome to Mediterrano where we take a coastal approach to the splendor of Mediterranean cuisine. Our valued customers will find tantalizing dishes from the coasts of Spain, Greece, Italy, Morocco and many more of the Mediterranean sea's bordering countries. We invite you to come experience our culinary vision for coastal Mediterranean, where explosive flavor profiles are delicately balanced through a fresh regional platform. Mediterrano, where exquisite food is complimented with top class hospitality.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Van%20Van%20Cuban%20Cafe?-Naples-Restaurants-2-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1a/35/9b/2b/anything-you-order-you.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Welcome to Van Van Cuban Cafe! Our restaurant offers food lovers the opportunity to experience the authentic flavors of Cuban Cuisine in a stylish way. Our menu focuses on traditional Cuban preparations, but also displays some famous international dishes. Van Van Cuban Cafe is the place where families and friends can gather and celebrate while enjoying our homemade delights.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Lamoraga?-Naples-Restaurants-3-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0e/36/10/15/our-best-selling-lamoraga.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Lamoraga Restaurant showcases a Mediterranean Fusion and Tapas Cuisine restaurant in Naples, Florida. We offer a wide variety of international dishes, delicious food, fresh seafood, and refreshing cocktails.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Bha!%20Bha!%20Persian%20Bistro?-Naples-Restaurants-4-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/02/48/16/b7/fresh-grills.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>This is an elegant high end and fine dinning innovative and classic "Persian" bistro for adults. Food: It offers arrays of faboulas dishes with roots in Iran but with modern Florida flair and influnce. The menu is vast, it concentrates on savory elegant braised lamb in many different varieties, Eggplant, fresh Fl seafood, grilled kebabs of beef, chicken. Lamb rule here. Other dishes such as duck, quail and seafood with exquisite Persian saffron rices are all fabulously tempting and present here. Full bar. Excellent wine list (No BYOB) signature boutique wines. Dress code: Florida casual but elegant and proper please. No tank tops or flip flops. No kids menu, No strollers. No crying babies please. Outside requests: (weather permitting) are accpted but not guaranteed. Dine under the stars in this highly acclaimed international destination. Bha! Bha! Bistro is referred to as " Jewel of the Crown" of the cosmopolitan 5th Ave in Naples FL. NYT calls it: "Persian Perfection"</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Caffe%20dell'Amore?-Naples-Restaurants-6-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/1d/13/2e/19/caffe-dell-amore.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Italian Restaurant in Naples, Florida Remember that wonderful vacation you took to Italy with your beloved awhile back? You strolled through the streets taking in the sites, the art, the culture, and the joy of living around you. You stopped to eat in one of the many wonderful trattoria, intimate and romantic, savoring the best Italian food, drinking great wine, talking with loved ones and just enjoying life. Caffe dell'Amore allows you to recreate that experience. Our Italian restaurant in Naples, Florida, serves authentic meals made with generations-old recipes passed down from chef to chef. We cook with love and passion, offering you a taste of Italy while you enjoy the company of loves ones in an intimate setting. A Fine Dining Italian Restaurant Inspired by the great Italian tradition of quality at the table and in the glass, we are dedicated to seeking out the best ingredients for our dishes.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/T-Michaels%20Steak%20and%20Lobster?-Naples-Restaurants-7-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/11/a9/29/26/beautiful-venetian-bay.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>T-Michaels Steak and Lobster is a fine dining Waterfront restaurant on Venetian Bay in Naples, Florida! We specialize in USDA Prime Steaks, Whole Maine Lobsters and Daily Caught Fish! Our Menu is Classic Steak and Lobster fare along with signature dishes from land, sea and earth. Our Daily Specials highlight locally caught fish with fresh ingredients, and our Wine list will be ever evolving with featured bottles weekly from around the globe.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Rumba%20Cuban%20Cafe?-Naples-Restaurants-8-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/16/96/c5/0c/rumba-cuban-cafe.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>In Cuba, Rumba is more than just a rhythm, it's a party! The moment you indulge in any of our signature dishes; we will put your taste buds to dance. Since opening in 2014, Rumba has delighted guests from all over the world. Bringing a little piece of Cuba closer to beautiful Naples, Florida.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Brooks%20Burgers?-Naples-Restaurants-9-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1b/6a/36/4e/famous-donut-burger.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Since 2010, Brooks Burgers - Burgers  Dogs has been committed to serving the perfect burger. Our all-natural, brilliantly cooked, deliciously crafted burgers are nationally recognized and locally famous. As a family-owned restaurant, we treat our customers like our own. Come try one of our unique burgers and join our family!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Noodles%20Italian%20Cafe%20%20Sushi%20Bar?-Naples-Restaurants-10-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/17/e0/37/d0/tuna-tataki.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Original Noodles since 1991, not the chain franchise. Local Owners Matt and Seth, Invite your family to join our family at Noodles Italian Cafe  Sushi Bar for a wonderful array of mouthwatering dishes for you to choose from. Homemade in house fresh pasta, fresh in house prepared desserts like Tiramisu made with real espresso coffee and imported Italian lady fingers. Our newly designed concept offers upscale Italian fare and classic favorites. Along with traditional sushi freshly made by our fantastic authentic trained sushi chefs. Try our own sushi creations like the "Big Daddy roll' filled with all our fresh fish and lightly tempura fried, or one of the traditional sushi creations like Tuna Tataki, prepared with "aaa grade" high quality tuna. Come and feast with us and all the flavors of the world.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Fuse%20Global%20Cuisine?-Naples-Restaurants-11-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0b/09/30/6e/lobster.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Fuse Global Cuisine offers a contemporary dinner, craft cocktails and martinis in relaxed, yet elegant atmosphere. Please join us as we continue to evolve and represent our heritage and love of cuisine.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/EJ's%20Bayfront%20Cafe?-Naples-Restaurants-13-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0f/4f/1a/0e/eggs-benedicts.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Naples Best Breakfast, served all day! Located at Bayfront, EJ's serves Naples Best Breakfast using the freshest local ingredients, served in a casual, energetic atmosphere. Enjoy the fresh breezes of Naples Bay on our outdoor dining area. EJ’s is a great place to meet your friends, enjoy a bottomless cup of coffee and casually visit for awhile. Get your work done or meet with business clients. EJ’s offers free WIFI. Pet friendly restaurant.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20European%20Bakery%20%20Cafe?-Naples-Restaurants-14-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0e/5a/10/6c/ciasto-kokosowo-wisniowo.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A little, charming, old european style cafe/restaurant. Serves excellent, homemade stuffed cabbage, hunter stew (bigos), goulash (beef stew) potato pancakes, homemade soups, crepes, pierogies etc....</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Captain%20%20Krewe?-Naples-Restaurants-16-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0b/e1/c0/35/grouper-sandwich.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Captain  Krewe serves up superb fresh seafood, prepared classically, in a relaxed and casual environment. Come as you are and enjoy a meal that rivals any fine dining restaurant. We also have a variety of beer, wine and non-seafood options available.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Truluck's%20Ocean's%20Finest%20Seafood%20%20Crab?-Naples-Restaurants-17-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/1c/e1/53/b6/prime-alaskan-king-crab.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Fresh redefined. Our chefs honor and elevate seafood dishes with superior ingredients, precise execution, and classic presentation. We are committed to serving the ocean’s finest seafood and fresh Florida Stone crab. From the traps to your table in less than 24 hours. Delight in the art of the cocktail, remarkable wines, captivating ambience and the service you deserve. Your table is waiting.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/La%20Trattoria?-Naples-Restaurants-18-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/16/fa/d6/fe/our-pizza.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located in the heart of Downtown Naples, La Trattoria has combined old world charm with a sense of family. Locally Owned and Operated, the familiar faces that run La Trattoria are the same that have been voted nationally “Travelers Best Everyday Dining “ a couple doors down at Caffe Milano. Luca Di Falco has extended his warm welcome down the street through the arms of La Trattoria. By Partnering with Massimiliano Tonni, an award winning craft cocktail creator, and by far one of the best front of the house managers in town and Domenico Foraggio, a third generation Pizza Chef from Naples Italy. La Trattoria offers an extensive selection of real Neapolitan style Personal Pizzas, Chef Domenico siting the reason it’s so Delicious is the simplicity of the ingredients and the many topping combinations the restaurant offers. La Trattoria also offers a full Pasta menu with options that make your mouth water and a unique Imported Beer Menu.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/First%20Watch?-Naples-Restaurants-20-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/03/ce/ef/fc/first-watch.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>First Watch specializes in delicious creations freshly-prepared to order. Their fresh, award-winning Breakfast, Brunch and Lunch dishes are made using only the best ingredients without the use of heat lamps or deep fryers. The best part is their creative menu features traditional favorites like omelets, pancakes, salads and sandwiches.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Ocean%20Prime?-Naples-Restaurants-23-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0f/5e/55/5a/ocean-prime.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Ocean Prime is an award winning modern American restaurant and lounge from renowned restaurateur Cameron Mitchell. With stunning settings, a vibrant energy, an impressive menu of seafood and steaks and truly exceptional service, Ocean Prime is an ideal place to socialize, talk business, celebrate and indulge.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Osteria%20Tulia?-Naples-Restaurants-24-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/07/8a/30/6e/osteria-tulia.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Osteria Tulia is Naples, Florida's first osteria, serving exquisitely prepared Italian peasant cuisine in the ambiance of a lovingly restored Italian farmhouse. Osteria Tulia is the vision of Sicilian-born Chef/Partner Vincenzo Betulia, a long-time Old Naples chef whose flavorful dishes have earned top culinary accolades and a passionate international following.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/USS%20Nemo%20Restaurant?-Naples-Restaurants-25-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0c/f2/a7/ea/uss-nemo.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A stylized sort of nautical setting, USS Nemo's cool, comfortable blue interior gives one just a hint of the old "Voyage to the Bottom of Sea" motif with round brass portholes and a mock periscope. The menu definitely appeals to those with a taste for the exotic as it successfully marries a seafood cornucopia with Asian cuisine. The service is impeccable and the entrees are styled in drop-dead gorgeous fashion. The Bento Boxes are marvelous conversation starters. Even the pickled ginger is made to look like a piece of art. It's easy to see why USS Nemo is popular with the crowd of the going place.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Hobnob%20Kitchen%20%20Bar?-Naples-Restaurants-26-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/05/33/8a/9a/time-to-hobnob.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>For creative American cuisine that is both fresh and simple, look no further than Naples own HobNob Kitchen  Bar. Executive Chef Tony Biagetti and Chef du Cuisine Jeremy Caprari are in constant collaboration to bring new trends and new takes on traditional American cuisine right to your table. Using the freshest and highest quality ingredients that are often sourced locally, they're able to offer up a truly unforgettable meal! For interesting takes on traditional favorites, order the Snapper in Crazy Water with tomato, fennel, and soft polenta or even our popular Meyer Lemon Short Ribs with lemon risotto, escarole, and pine nut gremolata. But HobNob Kitchen  Bar isn't only known for our incredible food, we have a truly impeccable bar. Designed for comfort and aided by swagger, it's the perfect spot to meet for a drink with friends! We have all of your favorite libations as well as a craft beer menu (including our own HobNob Ale!) And an ever-evolving wine list. Stop by and enjoy our daily happy hour from 4-6pm with half-off wells and wines and a special happy hour menu. When you're in the mood for a delicious, innovative, fresh meal, join us at HobNob Kitchen  Bar! Dinner Monday - Saturday 5 P.M - 10 P.M Sunday 5 P.M - 9 P.M</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Skillets?-Naples-Restaurants-27-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1b/10/32/66/start-your-day-with-scratch.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Great food made from scratch! The Skillets brand has proudly served the finest breakfast and lunch for 25 years with locations throughout Southern Florida. All of our delicious dishes are scratch-made from the finest ingredients available. Fresh-squeezed juices in frosted mugs, our custom-blend coffee beans ground per brew, homemade breads, biscuits, and scones, always fresh, seasonal fruits, skillets dishes, omelets, eggs any style, slow-roasted corned beef hash, thick-cut smokehouse bacon, french toast, light as feather waffles, crepes, and over-the-top pancakes. Lunch has a wide array of sandwiches, salads, wraps, tacos, panini, platters, and combos - all served in a beautiful setting by a staff that really cares about your satisfaction and happiness. If you haven't been to Skillets, it's time you come by and taste the difference. Dine In, Takeout, Delivery, and Catering are available.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Bistro%20821?-Naples-Restaurants-28-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/22/02/26/c9/pick-two-sea-bass-and.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>2022 is Bistro 821's 28th year in business. All these years we have prided ourselves as being the small locally owned Bistro on 5th Ave South. Friendly service, excellent food and a great atmosphere are our specialties. We are famous for our sea bass, prawns and snapper dishes.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/MR.%20BIG%20FISH?-Naples-Restaurants-29-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1b/ff/40/8f/mr-big-fish-shrimp.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Family owned Seafood , fresh fish ,grouper, craft beer, lobster ,shrimp, chowder, steaks, full bar ,liquor, beer, wine, fresh bread ,kid friendly, reservations accepted, outdoor seating patio. Covid 19 guidlines</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Jimmy%20P's%20Charred%20-%20Naples?-Naples-Restaurants-30-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/08/cf/67/7b/jimmy-p-s-butcher-shop.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>As you enter through the front doors, you will know that you have arrived in the finest steak and chop house when the sweet smoky air from the in- house smoker reaches your nose. The visible adjacent butcher shop allows our guests to see the action of our expert meat cutters readying the evening's special cuts. We will still offer a few seats in the butcher shop for the casual lunch crowd. Meanwhile, the new space will offer room to allow all of our quests to enjoy a daytime or evening meal at a comfortable table. The mood of this nostalgic dining area will be upbeat, high-energy and casual sophistication. This will be a friendly and relaxed place, not fancy or stuffy. The staff will work hard to make you feel at home. The action of the butchers, chefs, and the local crowd and the hustle and bustle of the service staff, will allow you to participate in the energy.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Cosmos%20Ristorante%20%20Pizzeria?-Naples-Restaurants-31-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/12/4f/60/1a/cosmos.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Cosmos Cafe  Pizzeria offers the finest in authentic and inspired Italian cuisine. Using only the freshest ingredients, our menu features fresh homemade pastas, specialty pizzas, seafood, sandwiches and more! Introducing his family’s generations-old recipes and the experience of his career, owner Gianluca Corso has given Cosmos Italian Cafe and Pizzeria that unique, intimate and irresistible Italian flare that you’ll find nowhere else.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Shula's%20Steak%20House?-Naples-Restaurants-32-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1a/f6/40/a8/22oz-dry-aged-ribeye.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Coach Don Shula's ability to dig into the details translated to a record-setting number of wins on the field. His consistent excellence entertained; his pursuit of perfection inspired; and his winning ways created lasting memories. We want every experience at Shula's Steak House to do the same for you. From the moment you enter, Coach's storied career sets the tone for an elevated take on the traditional steakhouse experience. Perfectly prepared steaks, and bold, craveable interpretations of classic steakhouse dishes are paired with attentive service that puts you front and center. We go above and beyond to make sure that each and every carefully considered detail comes together in a way that entertains, not overwhelms, so that you can focus on enjoying the moment and making memories with your guests. Whether you're celebrating an anniversary or just the end of the work week, your experience at Shula's Steak House will stick with you long after you've left the table.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20French?-Naples-Restaurants-33-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0e/4a/88/05/photo1jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Award-winning Chef Vincenzo Betulia offers casual French classics, lighter fare and coastal dishes in an informal, convivial and bustling neighborhood brasserie. The French is a slice of the Belle Epoque in the heart of Naples.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/BiCE?-Naples-Restaurants-36-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0e/86/ae/49/veal-milanese.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Experience the exquisite decor, tantalizing Italian cuisine and service paralleled to none. An exquisite culinary voyage right to the heart of Italy awaits you amid a decor which combines Old World elegance and modern chic. BiCE Ristorante offers exquisite Northern Italian cuisine, and superb service in an elegant atmosphere. Featuring homemade Pasta, Veal Ossobuco, Veal Chop Milanese and Tiramisu.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Caffe%20Milano?-Naples-Restaurants-37-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/17/22/d0/54/enjoy.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Caffé Milano opened its doors in 2015 from a concept inspired by Luca Di Falco, a veteran Managing Partner of BiCE Restaurant, offering a modern take on the classic Naples, presenting italian gourmet in a casual setting. His vision was to delivery the modern but rustic italian cuisine, from the south to the north of Italy. We can delight you with our homemade bread and pastas, our signature skizza (our innovated skinny and light pizza), a wide variety of sandwiches for lunch and authentic italian fresh dishes to satisfy our worldwide clientele all day long. We offer delicious handcrafted drinks and signature desserts such as our giant Tiramisu` or our Homemade Gelato prepared a' la minute. If you are looking for an ideal spot, Caffé Milano should be your first stop of the day and your last stop at night!!!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Jane's%20Cafe?-Naples-Restaurants-38-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0d/0b/61/88/our-beautiful-patio.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A fantastic Downtown Naples Garden location with bubbling Koi Pond on the front Courtyard and cosy garden patio at the back, yet a cool interior to relax in during these hot summer days. Offering Breakfast  Lunch with yummy desserts too. All of our dishes are prepared with totally fresh produce delivered daily, our chefs work with passion to cook made to order plates including vegetarian  vegan meals. Lots of healthy Fruits, homemade Soups, daily Quiche, variety of Eggs Benedicts, Omlettes, delicious Sandwiches  Panini, Seafood Crepes, along with totally comforting French Toast, Crepes, Belgian Waffles, Yogurt Parfaits. All day Brunch is served, sample delightful dishes with a glass of Champagne Cocktail,such as Mimosa, Strawberry Orange Mimosa, our favorite Fruit Lemonade Mocktails, gourmet Espresso drinks or a variety of Teas. Relax with family  friends or simply bring the paper or a good book  enjoy watching the world go by.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Alberto's%20on%20Fifth%20Fine%20Italian%20Restaurant?-Naples-Restaurants-39-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/05/f5/a0/1a/alberto-s-on-fifth-fine.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>WELCOME TO ALBERTOS RESTAURANT Chef Alberto Varetto creates the finest in contemporary Northern Italian cuisine.His culinary interpretations emphasize seasonal ingredients, while creatively respecting the great traditions of Italian gastronomy, The glory of Italian cooking is fresh ingredients, served at their peak and handled in a way that flatters, rather than masks, their personalities.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Bleu%20Provence?-Naples-Restaurants-40-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/09/68/14/9d/bleu-provence-award-winning.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Bleu Provence, Award Winning French Restaurant in Naples, FL. Zagat-Rated and Wine Spectator Grand Award Recipient.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Tommy%20Bahama%20Restaurant%20%20Bar?-Naples-Restaurants-41-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/05/c6/47/aa/tommy-bahama-s-tropical.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located on charming, historic Third Street South, a short walk from the Naples pier, the original Tommy Bahama Restaurant  Bar is the ideal spot for lunch, dinner, or happy hour. You will instantly feel like a Florida local when treated to unparalleled hospitality on the festive, spacious patio or watch the culinary team in action from a table near the open kitchen.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/M%20Waterfront%20Grille?-Naples-Restaurants-42-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/15/47/22/9f/filet-mignon.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Designed as a contemporary Naples waterfront restaurant, M Waterfront Grille is refined and engaging, featuring Cutting Edge Continental Cuisine with an emphasis on Fresh Seafood, Steaks, Handmade Pasta, Organics and Tapas plates. M Waterfront Grille is both a local favorite as well as a destination restaurant offering dynamic flavor profiles and polished attentive service. The award winning comprehensive Wine List showcases highly allocated vintages and large format selections. Enjoy spectacular Venetian Bay views with Five Unique Venues at the Best Waterfront Restaurant in Naples, FL. View our updated menus on our web site.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Molto%20Trattoria?-Naples-Restaurants-44-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/09/89/db/8a/molto-trattoria.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>"simply my mom in the kitchen" is our motto and she shares traditional family recipes! All our pastas and sauces are homemade and we pride ourselves on using only the very best quality ingredients. Our pizza chef came all the way from Napoli to create the finest neapolitan pizza for you to enjoy. We invite you to come and dine with us! Serving lunch and dinner. We also offer delivery so you may dine poolside or on the beach.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Pazzo!%20Cucina%20Italiana?-Naples-Restaurants-45-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/16/43/b1/1e/main-dining-room.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Nationally Known ... Locally Loved! Pazzo! is celebrating its 25th year as Naples best, most fun and creative Italian restaurant! With original handcrafted recipes that have stood the test of time along with the sincere friendly service Pazzo! is known for, Pazzo! (which means crazy in Italian) offers a 150 bottle wine list, over 50 unique craft cocktails and spirits along with farm fresh quality ingredients, artisan cheeses, unique small batch olive oils, homemade pasta and the finest quality meats and seafood.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Swan%20River%20Seafood%20Restaurant?-Naples-Restaurants-46-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/74/52/2d/lobster-boat-raw-bar.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A cozy New England restaurant  raw bar, Swan River Seafood consistently brings the freshest varieties of the sea in delicious ways to happy Naples' locals and visitors. Enjoy wine and oysters at The Lobster Boat Raw Bar and dine on the largest selection of fresh market fish in Naples. The New England vibe continues out to our newly renovated patio booths. Enjoy Florida breezes as you savor the freshest fish with the friendliest service. The seafood market is open daily providing the home cook with pristine fresh fish and delicious prepared delicacies. Visit Swan RIver Seafood for local Stone Crabs October to May.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Chops%20City%20Grill?-Naples-Restaurants-47-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1a/69/38/f8/dining-room.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Our menu features the lowest prices on American, certified Japanese and Australian wagyu steaks, in the country and dry aged Prime beef. The menu is rounded out by affordable “butcher shop” cuts, an array of fresh vegetables, creative entrees, loads of seafood and sushi that can only be complemented by our ‘affordable to extravagant’ wine list, whiskey bar featuring over 100 whiskeys and innovative craft cocktails. Chops City Grill has an elegant dining room that presents our guests with an intimate setting paired with gracious service. With wood paneling, luxurious drapes, relaxed seating and modern lighting this dining room tips its hat to the traditional steak houses of the past.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Campiello?-Naples-Restaurants-48-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/13/48/66/21/the-patio.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Housed in Historic Naples Mercantile Building, Campiello offers inventive Italian cuisine inspired by a traditional Tuscan country cooking, with an open kitchen and many wood-roasted and rotisserie-grilled specialties. Join us for the "Italian Taste Tour" - a series of month long culinary salutes to Italy's greatest regions. The restaurant features a lavish interior inspired by Michelangelo-designed Villa San Michele in Friesole, Italy-replete with Murano light fixtures, fine leather chairs and banquettes, polished Venetian plaster, and hand painted Florentine murals</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Three60%20Market?-Naples-Restaurants-49-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/03/69/c8/bd/three60-market.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Stop by for the best wine prices in Naples! Outside open air seating for breakfast, brunch and lunch on our waterside decks. All staff wear masks. We feature a great wine selection and unique delicacies including artisan cheeses, breads, baked goods, and pastas from Naples Pasta. Breakfast is served 8 till 4, lunch from 11 till 4. Three60 Market has that Southern Florida feeling with a taste of Soho Chic right here on Bayshore Drive in Naples. Everything on our menu is a "creation" - made fresh, from scratch, every day. We promise you an upbeat experience that you won't soon forget whether you come for breakfast or lunch.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Brambles%20English%20Tea%20Room?-Naples-Restaurants-50-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/5f/1d/74/devonshire-cream-tea.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>English Tea Room serving traditional afternoon teas and a full lunch menus. Over 40 different teas, coffee, soft drinks, wine, champagne and beer</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Sails%20Restaurant?-Naples-Restaurants-51-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/18/29/51/95/5th-ave-room.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Opened in February 2018, Sails quickly became the talk of the town, earning the highest accolades possible both from the region’s restaurant reviewers and its discerning patrons. Much of the media's focus is what sets Sails apart: attention to detail at every level throughout the experience. From its exclusively-sourced pristine ingredients to friendly five-star service, co-founding partners Veljko Pavicevic and Corinne Ryan created a dining haute spot where the finest flavors of France, Italy and Greece evoke fond memories of a coastal European getaway with each delicious bite.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Claw%20Bar?-Naples-Restaurants-52-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/12/62/d9/8f/seafood-tower.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Claw Bar brings chic hotel dining to the Bellasera Resort in downtown Naples. Featuring gracious hospitality and spectacular cuisine, The Claw Bar specializes in seafood towers assembled right before your eyes in our open kitchen, as well as a full array of seafood entrees, southern-influenced dishes, and regionally-inspired cuisine. The Claw Bar prides itself on using locally-grown and locally-sourced ingredients whenever possible. Indoor and outdoor dining options available.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Michelbob's%20Championship%20Ribs%20%20Steaks?-Naples-Restaurants-53-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0d/47/90/19/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Michelbob's has been family-owned and operated since 1979. Features imported baby back ribs, pulled pork, sliced pork, sliced beef, steaks and homemade onion rings, cole slaw and baked bbq beans. Winner of over 100 awards for great food and voted "Best Restaurant" in S.W. Florida. Casual family dining with a full bar. The decor is worth the trip by itself.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Alice%20Sweetwaters%20Bar%20%20Grille?-Naples-Restaurants-54-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/01/f7/c7/4a/children-s-chicken-strips.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Alice Sweetwater's has been serving locals and tourists in Naples for 31 years. Opening in December 1988 serving our famous lightly battered deep fried shrimp, fresh grouper and oysters along with a fabulous pork tenderloin, fresh salads, great burgers and many other homemade items. Enjoy dining inside or relax on our patio out back. Both feature full liquor bars with cold beer and great wines. We offer a very casual and relaxed atmosphere. Come on in you will not be disappointed.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Bellini%20Italian%20Restaurant%20And%20Bar?-Naples-Restaurants-57-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1c/97/1a/6c/bellini-italian-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Newly relocated to the Iconic Chardonnay location. Same great Italian dishes and services as always.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Vergina%20Restaurant?-Naples-Restaurants-58-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/17/f6/e7/12/main-dining-room.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>*WE MAKE FOOD WITH PASSION FOR LASTING IMPRESSIONS* Our Executive Chef is featuring primarily Italian, but also French and Spanish Cuisine. Offering many specialties from the wider Northern Mediterranean Cuisine. Through his culinary creations our Chef presents renown culinary expertise with a refined touch and great attention to detail. The tradition at Vergina continues with many recipes that have not changed since its establishment in the year 2000.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Continental?-Naples-Restaurants-59-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/07/38/ad/10/the-continental.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>D'Amico's The Continental American Provisions and Craft Bar is Naples newest addition to Third Street South.The perfect blend of steak house + craft bar, The Continental adds ever more allure with a meticulously designed indoor and outdoor setting of New York Steakhouse meets 1920's Parisian Bistro. Explore our fare from land  sea while enjoying classic libations with a twist. Our steaks are hand cut by a fifth generation butcher, using only the finest Prime, Wagyu and Piedmontese beef. We feature a 30 seat Craft Cocktail Bar and live entertainment seven days a week.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Cafe%20Normandie%20Naples?-Naples-Restaurants-60-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/1d/b4/3a/cc/finalist.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>French Bistro with a real French Chef We propose on-site or take away lunch and dinner from the French baguette sandwich or quiche to the traditional Beef Bourguignon, Escargots and homemade desserts. Catering and privatization available for your party on request. We propose a friendly but safe and sanitized service.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Dock%20at%20Crayton%20Cove?-Naples-Restaurants-62-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1a/f6/bd/96/the-dock-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A NAPLES ORIGINAL WATERFRONT RESTAURANT The waterside ambiance of the Dock is as compelling as its food. The Dock is a little piece of Naples’ history – in fact, for lots of locals and visitors, we’re practically part of the family. And we think that’s because we give people what Naples is all about – Bay views, great food and a laid-back attitude. Seafood has been a decades-long love affair at the Dock, an open-air restaurant overlooking Naples Bay in historic Crayton Cove at the City Dock. Here, we prepare the freshest fish with Caribbean and Latin influences; our menu also offers tasty salads and sandwiches, and tempting beef, poultry and pasta dishes, as well as innovative daily specials and a surprisingly affordable wine list.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Outback%20Steakhouse?-Naples-Restaurants-66-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0d/88/09/58/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Outback Steakhouse, the home of juicy steaks, spirited drinks and Aussie hospitality. Find our location in Naples off 9th Street North and Castello Drive across from Staybridge Suites and Publix.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/La%20Pescheria?-Naples-Restaurants-67-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/18/6d/e4/64/la-pescheria.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Italian seafood recipes from Southern Italy with fresh fish delivered everyday Cozy and rustic style Trattoria</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Pinchers?-Naples-Restaurants-68-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0e/4d/d1/8c/dish.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Fresh is everything to a seafood restaurant, especially ours, and we try our best to deliver fresh seafood to your table each and every visit. Local fishermen and crabbers leave our shores daily and guide their boats out into the Gulf of Mexico to fish on behalf of Pinchers. They return each night with the best that the Gulf has to offer. They bring this precious catch to us and are one of the primary reasons for our success. In 2007, we purchased the Island Crab Company on Pine Island to serve as a fresh seafood facility for our restaurants. By having our own local facility, we can deliver fresh fish and shellfish to the table faster and fresher - whether its Grouper, Blue Crab, Stone Crab or some of the wonderful fish that you'll see highlighted as specials of the day. Local Fisherman fish Local Waters for a Local Restaurant. You can't get a more Southwest Florida experience than that! Pinchers - Florida Seafood, Florida Style. 12 Locations throughout SW Florida!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Yabba%20Island%20Grill?-Naples-Restaurants-70-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0a/f4/dc/f6/yabba-offers-a-wide-range.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>AFFORDABILITY ON FIFTH! Specializing in fresh Florida stone crab, great steaks and seafood and featuring our half priced wine list! You won’t find great wine more affordable anywhere or stone crab and steaks any better! With sultry ocean blues, accents of silver and deep mahogany woods, Yabba Island Grill may be the sexiest and most affordable restaurant on 5th!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Village%20Pub?-Naples-Restaurants-71-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/13/8d/16/e1/nice.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Local American Pub with a nautical touch. Sitting overlooking Venetian Bay. Dine on the bay or inside. Entertainment Thursday thru Saturday nights</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Alexander's%20Restaurant?-Naples-Restaurants-72-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/10/49/a7/a4/alexander-s-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Alexander's is a small European style Restaurant. Chef owned and operated with his wife Monika from Germany have been serving Neapolitans for more than twenty years. Serving lunch and dinner October thru May, Chef Alexander and his Professional staff will look forward to meet you and hope that you will have a memorable dining experience.We offer a casual fine dining in a elegant but comfortable dining room along with a beautiful garden setting. (Zagat Rated)</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Aqua?-Naples-Restaurants-74-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/12/fa/0c/b1/aqua-seafood-staeks-and.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Fine dining fresh local seafood happy hour 4-8 daily live entertainment whole fish De-boned table side banana foster</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Dorona?-Naples-Restaurants-75-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/18/5a/ea/8f/grasfed-ribeye-steak.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Dorona features an approachable main menu along with a special menu featuring the finest custom cuts of beef available from select farms across the USA. Menu items include re-invented sandwiches and burgers, pasta dishes, fresh salads, seafood, chicken, pork, lamb, and duck offerings. Dorona also has a lively bar that includes craft beers, hand craft cocktails, and wines on tap.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Barbatella?-Naples-Restaurants-77-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/fc/c8/54/interior.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>For a dining experience that is reminiscent of old world Italy yet still modern and fresh, look no further than Barbatella. We are a family-friendly Italian restaurant in Old Naples serving delicious food made with fresh, high-quality ingredients. Our menu explores the rustic landscapes of Italy, offering a diverse sampling of the cuisine from different regions.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Le%20Indya%20Naples%20-%20Authentic%20Indian%20Cuisine?-Naples-Restaurants-78-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/9f/27/91/chicken-tikka-masala.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>One of the Most Authentic Indian Restaurants Naples Has Ever Seen. Here at Le Indya, we offer authentic Indian cuisine in Naples with a bit of a classic twist. Our Passionate chefs prepares authentic dishes that are rich with the traditional ingredients and flavours of regional offerings, enhanced by the Traditional family way.. We have spicy and non-spicy variants, as well as vegetarian ,Vegan ,gluten free ,and non-vegetarian choices to cater to all palates and preferences. From hand-picked seafood choices to exotic meats, you are sure to find a dish that will deliver a new experience. We source our Spices from the best markets in India, in order to bring a completely authentic flavour to each dish. Get in Touch with us!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Bar%20Tulia%20-%205th%20Avenue?-Naples-Restaurants-79-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/07/3a/cd/72/bar-tulia.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Bar Tulia, Southwest Florida's first Italian gastropub, welcomes wine enthusiasts, beer drinkers and foodies alike. This new neighborhood eating bar pays homage to hidden gems from small wineries and craft breweries locally and abroad, while offering an all-day menu of modern pub fare in the coolest surroundings to satisfy the palate of even the late-night crowd.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Chez%20Boet-French%20Home%20Cooking?-Naples-Restaurants-81-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/06/82/fa/0d/chez-boet-french-home.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Established in 2003, Chez Boet is a chic neighborhood bistro serving country French cuisine and owned and operated by Lisa  Philippe Boet. The menu reflects the Boets' experiences in France spending long weekends in the French countryside with family and friends, cooking traditional, home-style dishes with what came from the family farm and garden.Under the direction of Lisa Boet, Chez Boet's culinary team prepares dishes including Pate Maison, French Onion Soup, Bouillabaisse, Roasted Orange Duck, Boeuf Bourguignon, along with fresh local seafood and authentic Moroccan tagines, served with locally grown, seasonal produce.Cheese and Chocolate Fondue is also on the menu. Chez Boet has a full bar with cocktails prepared by Philippe Boet, varied wine list, and covered terrace for outdoor dining. Private parking in rear. Healthy children's menu and pet-friendly terrace. Proud founder of Naples Originals, the finest independent restaurants. Chez Boet has been named the City of Naples first certified green restaurant.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Mino?-Naples-Restaurants-82-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0b/1e/da/e3/mino-italian-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We serve Neapolitan Style Pizzas We offer a Full Bar Service We serve authentic Italian food - Restaurant We’re open Tuesday thru Sunday. 5-9pm...last call for food and beverage is 8:45pm. Thank you and look forward to your visit. Mino</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Spanky's%20Speakeasy?-Naples-Restaurants-83-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0e/7f/07/1b/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A Naples Landmark for over 35 years, serving Breakfast, Lunch and Dinner. We are known for Naples best Prime Rib and Fresh Seafood. Enjoy our Salad Bar in the bed of a 1924 Ford Model T. Daily Early Bird Specials and a Full Service Bar with daily Happy Hour. Dine inside with antiques and vintage memorabilia, or on Naples best Open Air Waterfront Patio.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Cibao%20Grille?-Naples-Restaurants-84-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/02/37/d6/94/scallops-with-baby-arugula.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Business Hours: Mon-Fri 11:00 am - 1:30 pm 5:00 pm - 9:00 pm Saturday 5:00 pm - 9:00 pm Sunday Closed</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Carrabba's%20Italian%20Grill?-Naples-Restaurants-87-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0e/28/62/9b/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Enjoy authentic Italian for dine-in, carryout, delivery or catering.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Ridgway%20Bar%20%20Grill?-Naples-Restaurants-88-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0f/76/1a/41/salmon.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Chef-owned restaurant in historic Old Naples, two blocks from the Naples beaches, serving lunch and dinner daily and brunch on Saturdays and Sundays. Open daily throughout the year including all holidays. With expansive indoor and outdoor seating, loved for its welcoming atmosphere and French-influenced American cuisine.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Riverwalk%20at%20Tin%20CityR?-Naples-Restaurants-93-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0e/43/c0/8d/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Riverwalk at Tin City® serves seafood dishes for lunch and dinner to the Naples, FL area.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Bevy?-Naples-Restaurants-95-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/18/00/4d/34/outdoor-open-air-at-night.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>New American cuisine, happy hour, dinner, brunch, full bar  craft cocktails in a unique indoor-outdoor space with a vertical garden. A fun, modern atmosphere with free valet in downtown Naples, FL off of 3rd Street. Gluten free, vegetarian, and vegan options available.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Industry%20Beer%20%20Barbeque?-Naples-Restaurants-96-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/16/ac/81/54/our-tacos-are-deliciousdon.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A warm, friendly place to gather. At our brewpub in Bayfront, we proudly offer our guests the chance to taste the best beers craft brewed locally in and around Naples, Florida. We have over 60 Florida craft beers on tap (plus several popular domestic drafts) with a constantly rotating selection. If that isn't enough we also feature over 80 bottles  cans of craft beers made around the US. Can't decide? We offer flights of 4 - 5 oz. pours to try. Still looking for more? We also have 8 wines on tap and a wide selection of bottled wine. Hungry? We also have a wide selection of food items made in-house!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Tropic%20Chill%20Deli?-Naples-Restaurants-97-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/05/53/35/9c/tropic-chill-deli.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Tropic Chill Deli is located near downtown Naples on the corner of US 41  Central Ave. Tropic Chill has been a local landmark PROUDLY serving the very BEST Sandwiches and Subs for over 20 YEARS! Come find out why we have been Voted BEST Sandwiches by the Naples Daily News Readers Choice Awards. We are open Monday-Friday serving Breakfast and Lunch for Dine-in, Take-out or FREE Delivery Service.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/I%20Love%20Curry?-Naples-Restaurants-98-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/1c/57/37/a2/logo.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>I Love Curry is a family owned Indian take-out restaurant. We have seating inside as well. I Love Curry started as a food truck and since has expanded.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/MiraMare%20Ristorante?-Naples-Restaurants-99-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/13/84/b9/82/a-random-night-at-miramare.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Real Italian Restaurant with a beautiful view of the bay. We have live music every night with wonderful staff. Perfect for a date night or even with a group of family and friends.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Hogfish%20Harry's?-Naples-Restaurants-100-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1c/75/22/5f/entrance-to-hogfish-harry.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Hogfish Harry's is a seafood restaurant in the heart of Naples that captures the essence of tropical dining through eclectic coastal delights  refined seafood creations. Naples veteran Chef Everett Fromm offers a lineup of fresh seafood, from shrimp and scallops to lobster, crab, mussels, and the house specialty Hogfish. Our beverage list focuses on wines from the United States, Europe, Australia,  South America, as well as tropical-inspired cocktails ranging from the classic mojito  sangria to signature drinks. With a vibrant, yet relaxed and casual ambiance  an island-inspired bar, we welcome you to relax, enjoy and indulge in cocktails  the days freshest catch. Call our Naples seafood place and fish restaurant to make a reservation!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Real%20Macaw?-Naples-Restaurants-102-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/22/00/99/ce/outdoor-dining.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Naples' best hidden gem! Award-winning eclectic casual and fine French-Caribbean cuisine in a Key West inspired setting. Serving Naples for more than 30 years. Come Join us for Dinner, Wine Tastings and the best Local Live Music.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Aurelio's%20Pizza?-Naples-Restaurants-104-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/03/3b/0d/3d/aurelio-s-pizza.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Aurelio's Pizza of Naples, located at the Coastland Center Mall (across from Cheesecake Factory). Enjoy a pizza dining experience for you and your family. We have a full menu including appetizers, salads, pasta, sandwiches, desserts and of course our award winning pizzas, including thin crust, thick crust and stuffed. We also have a full service bar with all your favorite beer, wine and spirits.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Olive%20Garden%20Italian%20Restaurant?-Naples-Restaurants-105-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0a/e3/3c/88/poulet.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>All of your favorites are just a few clicks away! View our menu online and Order Now for convenient Carside Delivery or come in for our famous never-ending first course of freshly baked breadsticks and your choice of homemade soup or garden fresh salad. Enjoy abundant portions of classic Italian favorites the whole family craves like the Tour of Italy, our irresistible Chicken Parmigiana, or everyone's favorite Fettuccine Alfredo, made fresh from our kitchen to your table. Gather together with the people you love over a meal worth sharing at Olive Garden. We're all family here.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Rosati's%20Pizza?-Naples-Restaurants-107-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/60/9b/1d/myrosatiscom.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Rosati's Pizza is committed to providing customers with signature Chicago style pizzas, pastas, and sandwiches that offer high quality, value and flavor. We've stayed true to our roots, continuing to use fresh ingredients and authentic Italian family recipes. Everything we do is history in the making.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Boathouse%20on%20Naples%20Bay?-Naples-Restaurants-108-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/12/e8/ac/7b/outdoor-seating-overlooking.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Seafood has been a decades-long love affair here in Southwest Florida. The Boathouse on Naples Bay, overlooking the glistening waters in historic Downtown Naples at the City Dock, has mastered this love affair like no other in the area. Wrapped in floor-to-ceiling windows, with seating indoors and out, the Boathouse on Naples Bay offers unprecedented views and a wonderful, historic and unpretentious atmosphere. We prepare the abundance of just-caught fish and seafood, flown in daily, with the freshest seasonal sides. Our menu also offers premium Midwestern beef and poultry, Old World pasta dishes, crisp, garden fresh salads, hardy sandwiches, succulent burgers, and innovative daily specials along with a surprisingly affordable wine list. The waterfront ambiance of the Boathouse on Naples Bay is as enticing as the food. We look forward to seeing you!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/South%20Street%20City%20Oven%20Bar%20and%20Music?-Naples-Restaurants-111-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0a/a8/63/ab/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A Philadelphia based concept, specializing in light italian, fresh brick oven pizza and of course, Philly Cheesesteaks. We offer a full bar with 45 seats, in addition to a full service dining room. Locally known for our selection of Craft Beers, featuring 54 taps, and our Live Music Events.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Turco%20Taco?-Naples-Restaurants-112-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/19/dc/bf/9e/photo4jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>At Turco Taco, our philosophy is the choices we make about the food we eat, and where it comes from, has a direct impact on our health and the environment. Therefore, we are committed to serving the freshest, organic locally grown produce with hormone and antibiotic free premium meats. Eating good food shouldn't be hard, thats' why we are happy to accommodate many diet restrictions.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Fish%20Restaurant?-Naples-Restaurants-113-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0e/1f/22/3a/fish-restaurant-naples.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Romantic indoor and outdoor waterfront dinning featuring a full range of culinary delights for everyone to enjoy, which also include fish.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/Wharf%20Tavern?-Naples-Restaurants-118-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/05/b4/92/8b/moon-lit-2.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Specializing in New England Seafood. Live MAINE Lobster, Ipswich fried Clams, Scallops, Fish n' Chips, Calamari, Jumbo Shrimp, Quahog Chowder, Lobster Bisque, Zuppa di Pesci, Seafood Fra Diavolo, to name a few ... And from the land, Chicken Marsala, N.Y. Sirloin, Filet Mignon, blackened Chicken Pasta, and more. Come and sit wharf side, or inside in our dining room that is decorated with a decidedly nautical/seashore theme.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/Naples/The%20Parrot%20Bar%20and%20Grill?-Naples-Restaurants-123-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/04/7b/ca/10/the-parrot-bar-and-grill.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title> </image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

</urlset>