<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1">
<script async="false" type="text/javascript" src="chrome-extension://fnjhmkhhmkbjkkabndcnnogagogbneec/in-page.js"/>
<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Wicked%20Dolphin%20Distillery?-CapeCoral-Attractions-1-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/1c/b6/21/aa/wicked-dolphin-distillery.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Wicked Dolphin Distillery is Florida's Famous most awarded craft distillery located in Cape Coral, FL! We offer free tours and tastings every Tuesday, Thursday, Friday  Saturday. Please check with our website to reserve space. Distillery Tour and Tasting Hours: Tuesday and Saturday tours are at noon, 1, 2, 3  4pm, Thursday tours are at noon, 1, 2, 3, 4  5pm, Friday tours are at 2, 3, 4,  5pm Saturday tours are at noon, 1, 2, 3  4pm Distillery Gift Shop Hours: Monday-Wednesday: 9am-5pm Thursday  Friday: 9am-7pm Saturdays 11am-5pm</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Cape%20Coral%20Farmers%20Market?-CapeCoral-Attractions-2-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/11/4c/78/2a/the-concourse.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Cape Coral Farmers Market is open, every Saturday, from 8a-1p Located in downtown Cape Coral at SE 47th Terr.  SE 10th Pl, in Club Square. The Cape Coral Farmers Market has been a favorite Saturday morning destination for 26 years. Over the years, we have grown to over 125 vendors. We like to think that we have all the delicious foods and local crafts that you love to shop for. Fresh, local  healthy fruits and veggies, including Certified Organic produce, are the core of the market along with homemade and handmade foods and crafts. Fresh baked breads  pastries, homemade pickles, jams  jellies, Gulf fresh seafood, fresh meats, homemade pet treats, handcrafted soaps, essential oils, local honey, made-on-site guacamole, fresh, cut flowers, native plants  trees are just some of the fantastic products available.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Four%20Mile%20Cove%20Ecological%20Preserve?-CapeCoral-Attractions-3-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/04/c1/f7/88/four-mile-cove-ecological.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The boardwalk is always full of birds, reptiles, bugs, etc. A real naturalist's dream. At the end of the boardwalk is the river. An observation dock is there to rest and take in the nature. Also there, are kayak rentals, and a number of patriotic statues, including a copy of the Iwo Jima flag rasing statue.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Lovegrove%20Gallery%20%20Gardens?-CapeCoral-Attractions-4-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0a/b6/0b/f6/lovegrove-gallery-garden.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Lovegrove Gallery  Gardens is the international headquarters for Florida artist, Leoma Lovegrove and one of the most colorful destinations in the sunshine state. The gallery showcases Lovegrove's original art and it is here where you can step into her techinicolor world of tropical artistic flair and experience the authentic island style life of an artist. Paint your own Florida souviner in her world famous botanical waterfront gardens (Paint and brushes included). Or paint your very own coconut postcard to keep or mail back home (no box needed- mails as is). You can also paint your own painting in the garden with the help of Vino's Picasso (Seasonal Nov-April). You can also enjoy homemade ( "Love Boat Ice Cream")ice-cream right out of a real coconut shell and guess what? You can keep the shell and take it back home to remind you of the happy memories you made while visiting one of Florida's most popular historic landmarks and destinations.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Wigert's%20Bonsai?-CapeCoral-Attractions-5-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/05/ba/5f/49/wigert-s-mango-grove.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Florida's premier bonsai nursery. Open 7 days a week. Retail and Wholesale. Bonsai trees , supplies , classes, bonsai pots</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Rotary%20Park%20Environmental%20Center?-CapeCoral-Attractions-6-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/04/a0/7f/f8/rotary-park-environmental.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Nature park featuring multiuse trails, flower gardens, wildlife observation towers  a dog run.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Fellowship%20Park?-CapeCoral-Attractions-8-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/11/e3/d1/94/photo4jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The park has a splash pad, shaded kids playground, swings, restrooms and is adjacent to a cafe. A great place to lets kids run around for a few hours on a hot day.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Sun%20Splash%20Family%20Waterpark?-CapeCoral-Attractions-9-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/07/b2/15/9a/sun-splash-family-waterpark.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Whether you prefer to ride heart-pounding water slides or simply soak up some rays, this water park is a perfect family destination.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Veterans%20Memorial%20Park?-CapeCoral-Attractions-11-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/15/60/4c/e7/fb-img-1542203359606.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>This 4.2 acre neighborhood park is a popular location for bocce leagues to host friendly competitions and a great place to take kids to enjoy the playground and a picnic, or play a game of basketball.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Matlacha%20Community%20Park?-CapeCoral-Attractions-12-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/13/46/76/7e/fishing-pier.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>9 acres on the waterfront with a boat launch, fishing pier, basketball court  playground.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Cape%20Coral%20Historical%20Museum?-CapeCoral-Attractions-13-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/04/c9/86/8e/cape-coral-historical.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Cozy museum displaying diverse exhibits dedicated to the history of the Cape Coral area.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Classic%20Auto%20Restoration%20Specialist?-CapeCoral-Attractions-14-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/10/6c/0a/af/front-of-building.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We have one of the largest collections of automobile, gas and oil memorbilia collections in Southwest Florida. Also on site is our fully functioning restoration shop where you can see cars being restored. Come see all the classic antique gas, oil and auto items in our museum and then stroll out among the classic cars in progress or on display. Monday to Friday 8am to 5pm.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Cultural%20Park%20Theatre?-CapeCoral-Attractions-15-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0a/ca/36/c4/the-exterior.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Performing arts theater in Cape Coral, Florida</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Prairie%20Pines%20Preserve?-CapeCoral-Attractions-20-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/12/2a/cc/98/prairie-pines-preserve.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Nature preserve featuring scenic trails for challenging hikes, biking  wildlife viewing.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/CrossFit%20ENG?-CapeCoral-Attractions-22-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/16/d6/f8/57/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>More than just a gym. CrossFit ENG is designed to create an atmosphere of learning, achievement, and success. We educate and train our athletes with a hands-on approach to fitness. We understand that physical fitness is only one chapter in the life long journey towards optimal health and wellness.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Matlacha%20Bat%20House%20Park?-CapeCoral-Attractions-23-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/11/10/37/39/the-other-side-of-the.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>​Bat House park is a small park on Matlacha island that is perfect for fishing and enjoying the view of the water. The park is named after the bat house which sits a few feet out over the water from the edge of the overlook.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Fishing%20Charters,%20Inc.?-CapeCoral-Attractions-28-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/04/4e/56/1e/fishing-charters-inc.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Charters available in the following locations: fort myers - sw florida area, orlando, and sebastian inlet at fishing charters, inc., we dedicate ourselves to bringing customers and captains together for a fishing adventure of a lifetime. All of our boats meet us coast guard standards and our captains are insured, licensed and seasoned professionals. Located in matlacha (pronounced mat-la-shay) island florida, near cape coral in the ft. Myers area, matlacha is a quaint little town between cape coral and pine island. Matlacha has some of the best restaurants in the area for the freshest seafood and all are right on and overlooking the tropical waters of matlacha pass. Most of our restaurants have live bands almost every night, making your dining experience a memorable one. It also has some of the most unique gift shops and local art galleries in the area including the art gallery of leoma lovegrove known worldwide for her art and paintings. We offer inshore saltwater fishing in the ft. Myers sw florida area, orlando area, and sebastian inlet. We have available boats including flats back country boats, bay boats, to a 24 foot tri toon in matlacha, where we have inshore saltwater fishing charters, eco nature tours and dolphin and manatee tours aboard the miss matti. Do you have questions about our charters? Contact us today. The central florida lakes offer some of the best bass fishing in the country. One of the lakes we bass fish is the 18,000-acre, big lake tohopekaliga (big toho), rated one of the top five bass lakes in the country. The current lake record is a 16.5-pound florida largemouth bass. We have several captains with bass boats and bay boats on big lake toho.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Cape%20Coral%20Sport%20Complex?-CapeCoral-Attractions-29-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/1c/ca/35/1a/cape-coral-sport-complex.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A 52-acre park hosting league games with lit soccer, softball  baseball fields, plus a playground.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Cape%20Coral%20Yoga%20%20Pilates?-CapeCoral-Attractions-30-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/19/a2/0c/cc/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A yoga boutique studio. Cape Coral Yoga  Pilates opened the doors in April 2019, as a safe place to learn to meditate, move and breathe. We offer a variety of classes, from Hatha Yoga, Hot Yoga and Mat Pilates. We offer showers, full boutique and classes at every level.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/MassageLuXe%20Cape%20Coral?-CapeCoral-Attractions-32-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/19/31/77/34/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>MassageLuXe invites you to come enjoy the many health benefits of Therapeutic Massage. Ease of stress, tension relief, improved immune system, and lower blood pressure are just a few of the many advantages gained with a continuous massage regimen; not to mention how great it feels to escape from the real world for an hour or two! We offer a variety of massages for every life stage!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Big%20Storm%20Brewing%20Company?-CapeCoral-Attractions-33-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/24/74/8f/de/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Founded in 2012, Big Storm Brewing Co. now has four taprooms in the Sunshine State</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Studio%208%20Dance?-CapeCoral-Attractions-34-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/18/49/56/29/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Studio 8 is truly a one of a kind experience. From our unique atmosphere, to our small personalized class sizes, we are dedicated to providing top quality dance education in a fun, positive environment. Whether your focus is technique, flexibility or you’re just looking for a fun new activity, you can find it here. Offering Summer Camp and Drop-in Classes for vacationing dancers!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Tropical%20Breeze%20Fun%20Park?-CapeCoral-Attractions-39-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/16/b5/f7/40/photo1jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Enjoy the area’s most deluxe, beautifully-landscaped Tropical miniature golf course featuring cascading waterfalls, adventurous holes and the signature world’s longest mini golf hole. The Tropical Breeze Extreme Outdoor laser tag is the first of its kind in this area. It features state-of-the-art equipment and deliver fast-paced, adrenaline-pumping fun.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Florida%20Biplane%20Rides?-CapeCoral-Attractions-50-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/21/ad/a2/37/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Offering sightseeing flights in an authentic open cockpit Biplane. Up to two people can fly together.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Botanical%20Brewing%20Company?-CapeCoral-Attractions-55-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/1c/ae/f4/ab/botanical-brewing-company.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Trendy Kava bar serving coffee, tea, kratom, and delicious Kava from around the world. Chill lounge atmosphere with pool table and plenty of community events. First non-alcoholic brewery of its kind in the USA. Specializing in a modern twist on traditional exotic plant botanicals drinks. A sober environment that welcomes all.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Shoot%20Center?-CapeCoral-Attractions-73-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/17/48/34/31/cz-bren-2-1.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Shoot Center exists to provide a safe and enjoyable recreational shooting experience through highly trained, welcoming staff in Southwest Florida.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Bowland%20Cape%20Coral?-CapeCoral-Attractions-74-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/05/66/3d/3d/check-out-our-vip-boutique.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>33-lane bowling alley featuring an arcade, full bar  an attached sports cafe with a patio.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Gulf%20Coast%20Kayak?-CapeCoral-Attractions-75-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/21/4f/d2/5d/gulf-coast-kayak-sunset.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Guided Kayak Ecotours of the Matlacha Pass Aquatic Preserve are offered daily. Our ecotours provide a guided exploration of the mangrove wilderness.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/AMC%20Merchants%20Crossing%2016?-CapeCoral-Attractions-77-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://fastly.4sqi.net/img/general/200x200/41843047_htNicbL3FYFJcd9N3T6D5HTP5GhZ1jLeUr0nACX1BxE.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located in the sunny Merchant's Crossing area of North Fort Myers, AMC Merchant's Crossing 16 offers a relaxing moviegoing experience with 16 auditoriums.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Art%20By%20San%20Paintings%20and%20Murals?-CapeCoral-Attractions-82-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/12/37/0b/e6/18-ft-x-12-ft-underwater.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Sandra Priest (San) is a professional, fine artist working with paintings on canvas, ceiling and wall murals, indoor and outdoor. Her career has spanned over 27 years, resulting in many residential and commercial works of art in the US and abroad. San is self taught in acrylics, oils and even sculpture. Her other website http://911up.com , is a 9/11 sculpture project consisting of 17, 8 ton cut out concrete sections from the original World trade center in New York City, now made into historical memorial sculptures.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Judy's%20Antiques%20and%20Estate%20Jewelry?-CapeCoral-Attractions-83-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1b/25/36/10/judy-s-jewelry-has-a.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We buy and sell Estate Jewelry - Diamonds, gold, silver, costume jewelry, old pocket and wrist watches (running or not), military items  small furniture.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Gator%20Mike’s?-CapeCoral-Attractions-85-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://gatormikes.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Photo-Nov-25-5-48-47-PM-scaled-1.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Endless fun in the sun awaits the entire family inside the gates of Gator Mike’s Family Fun Park! A visit to Gator Mike’s in Cape Coral, FL is one of the top things to do in Southwest Florida, so don’t miss out. Experience the excitement of Ziplining, Rock Climbing, Go-Karts, Mini Golf, Cutting Edge Arcade — all these and more fun activities here at Gator Mike’s.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Yacht%20Club%20Public%20Beach?-CapeCoral-Attractions-86-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://img.marinas.com/v2/840d23019749127ffb642fbfeb22db89e8bcfb44e57002b3a5fc252a3a6bcec2.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Sandy riverfront accessible beach with fishing pier, playground, restrooms, picnic shelters  BBQs.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/HeadPinz?-CapeCoral-Attractions-87-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://headpinz.com/images/gallery/HPCC/vip-1.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Large venue featuring bowling lanes, an arcade, sports TVs  a lounge with casual eats.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Masala%20Mantra%20Indian%20Bistro?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-1-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1a/cc/bc/6c/masala-mantra-indian.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We're Cape Coral's first Indian Restaurant. We're proud to be your neighbors  our No.1 Mantra is to bring in the finest Indian Cuisine to you</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Two%20Meatballs%20In%20The%20Kitchen%20-%20Cape%20Coral?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-2-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/1b/93/f0/1a/our-logo.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Generous portions of Italian pastas  pizzas dished up in roomy surrounds with TVs at the bar.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Gusto%20Cucina%20Italiana?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-3-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0a/3f/0c/dc/linguini-pescatore.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Our restaurant is about Authentic Italian Fresh food made to order. We specialize in Sicilian Saute and house made desserts. Award winning Food! Order online.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Fish%20Tale%20Grill%20by%20Merrick%20Seafood?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-4-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/19/81/d8/6a/hogfish-florentine.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Southwest Florida's premiere steak and seafood restaurant. Voted Best Seafood in Cape Coral for 8 years running. Our seafood Tower, Loaded Seafood Bloody Mary and many other offerings showcase the best seafood southwest Florida has to offer. Cutting edge craft cocktails, live music and destination bar. Whether you are joining us for lunch, Dinner or our famous Brunch you are sure to find something that fits your seafood palate. Indoor and covered outdoor seating are both available.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Lehne%20Burger%20Cape%20Coral?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-6-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0e/fe/d1/2a/lehne-burger.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Lehne Burger is a family-friendly restaurant where you can completely customize your Burger from scratch with more than 85,000 possible combinations, including vegan, vegetarian and gluten-free options. All Burgers are made to order and paired with a homemade Milkshake or an ice-cold Craft Beer you will be in “Burger Heaven”. Home of design your own burger</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Blue%20Dog%20Bar%20%20Grill?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-7-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0f/1b/70/dc/fish-taco-with-mango.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The goal of Blue Dog was to open a small, neighborhood restaurant in Matlacha, Florida the town we love. Our focus is on the small things that belong in a neighborhood restaurant. Being genuinely friendly, knowing the names of our guests and serving fresh local food at reasonable prices. Our hope is that the neighborhood grows to trust us and makes us an extension of their homes. The white boots (locally called 'Pine Island Reeboks') that 'Blue' wears on our logo are a nod to the rich past and current fishing history of Pine Island and Matlacha. These boots are worn by commercial fishermen all along the Gulf Coast from Texas to Florida. From our family, we'd like to give our thanks to every crabber, fisherman, shrimper, oysterman, and all the commercial fishermen on the entire Gulf Coast but particularly Matlacha and Pine Island, for the sacrifices you have made to carry on the traditions of your fathers. It's one of the things that makes us proud to call Matlacha and Pine Island home. This is a great community. We have weathered storms...together. We work hard...together. We play hard...together and when the day is done...those white boots are put out to dry. Come, eat well, have a brew and sit with us for a while...and the dog is happy.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Trattoria%20Ciao?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-9-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0f/75/f5/d8/house-cippino-ultimate.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>"Who are we?" Trattoria Ciao, an Italian dining experience. We specialize in freshly prepared Italian dinner dishes, steaks, seafood, chicken  veal, fresh catch and home of the 7 Layers of Love" (our house Lasagna) as well as homemade desserts, cappuccino, large imported wine selection  micro brews. Outdoor dining al fresco on the streetfront patio is unique. We carry a large winesj  micro beer selection, wine lover? Ask about "Our Stash" high end wine cabinet. See you soon Ciao! Jill  the family</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Twisted%20Lobster?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-10-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0f/72/62/68/twisted-lobster.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Twisted Lobster - Fresh - Flavorful - Unforgettable Whether you're looking for our Famous Twisted Clam Chowder, Lobster Varieties, our local choices to New England classics, you are sure not to be disappointed. Come get "Twisted" at the Twisted Lobster Seafood Grill, Cape Coral!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/New%20England%20Moorings?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-11-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/c3/55/93/bar-and-dining-room.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A few lines to introduce myself. My name is Al Whelan, I am from Boston and worked at a famous "waterfront dive" known as Kelly's Landing. A seafood business in a Catholic community with lines down the street, literally. I worked there for five summers and enjoyed every minute of it. My first date with the counter girl (she couldn't resist a man in a paper hat), my first kiss, etc. One rule was demanded, cooking with clean oil! In those days it was lard! Today we use canola oil both on the grill side and on the fry side... Most of our dinners are on the grill side. Fish shrimp, scallops, steaks, ribs, chicken and pork round off our menu. Our Irish Connoli is like a little piece of heaven. Topped off with sweet whipped cream. We've added a 6000 square foot patio surrounded by trees. A truly private and romantic spot. Also some added features such as a corn hole court.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/The%20Dek%20Bar?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-13-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/dc/0c/3c/the-dek.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We're best described by one of our many 5 Star Reviewers, J D "Real Florida" There is a reason The Dek has a loyal clientele. The thin crust pizza is great. The bartenders are friendly and competent. The patrons are working class. If you want beautiful, plastic people with too much make-up on and $700 blue jeans go somewhere else. If you want a fun time, with good music (I highly recommend Tequila Tom's acoustic guitar session almost every Sunday afternoon) come here. Dave J is correct it is not a place for kids. Well-behaved dogs are welcomed. :) It is a bar for adults, not politically correct cry babies who are easily offended by dirty jokes or tattoos.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Slate's?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-14-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/05/48/bc/c1/slate-s.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Causal fine dinning with a Cajun twist. Reservations encouraged.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/KEG%20%20COW?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-15-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0e/8a/d2/ff/you-know-you-want-one.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Cape Coral's Best Craft Beer Bar! Fresh Ingredients  Good Beer Along with Craft Beer, the company took a hard look at how to best compliment this specific concept related to food. For over decades, the burger has been an American staple. Instead of average beer and burgers, our company sought out the exceptional All American Burger. Our burgers begin daily with freshly ground meat that is a brand specific blend. To complement the burger, we have also worked with numerous bakeries to perfect our signature fresh-baked bun. To enhance the flavorful experience, it was important to offer fresh sides with our burgers. Fresh cut chips and fries were the perfect match to our juicy burgers.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Blanc?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-16-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0f/67/32/eb/yummm.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Blanc offers a wide variety of cuisine with selections of beef, chicken, fresh fish, lamb, and fresh vegetables, as well as featuring a robata grill. We offer "almost entrees": smaller plates designed for sharing. Blanc takes its influences from a variety of cultures, drawing on French, Asian  Latin flavors. Wonderful soups, salads, deserts, wines and cocktails round out the experience.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Perfect%20Cup?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-17-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/22/26/4c/6d/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Perfect Cup began as a coffee roasting shop, and expanded to a 7 day a week Breakfast/Lunch Cafe where we have won "best breakfast" and "Best Chowder" 2008,2009,2010. Our coffee is 2nd to none! We also won best breakfast 2011,2012,2013 and 2014 ! Also the chowder competition in 2011. We didn't compete in 2012 or 2013...Entered in 2014 and won again. That said, we have won the chowder competition ever year we have entered!!!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Ceno%20Grille?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-18-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/08/4b/85/62/ceno-grille.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Ceno Grille serves fresh, homemade Italian and Greek cuisine for lunch and dinner. For amazing food, service and atmosphere, look nowhere else! Ceno Grille is a small cozy restaurant perfect for the whole family. We have a large menu with many different options to choose from. Everything is fresh and homemade as if grandma made it herself, we don't even have a freezer! That's right, we make our own bread and everything is made in house. If you are in need of some recommendations, our Seafood Asparagus, Veal Piccitta, and Firehouse Chicken are just a few dishes that our customer's rave about. Our prices are affordable with our weekly dinner specials. Make sure to check us out on Mondays, we have pasta specials and it's something you don't want to miss. We also have a nice selection of draft beer and wine for you to enjoy with your meal. If you have a special event coming up, let us know. We have catering options available. Join us for Happy Hour, Monday thru Friday, 3pm-6pm for $1 off anything. So if you are looking for some excellent homemade food with great service (our wait staff is pretty amazing too), and great atmosphere give us a try for lunch or dinner today. You will be glad you did.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Misto%20Bar%20and%20Grill?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-22-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0e/a1/b1/3d/photo1jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>White tablecloth dining establishment serving an array of Cuisine from around the world. All foods are prepared in house including fresh bread to homemade desserts exotic dishes Italian Fresh Fish seafood Steaks Chops and pastas. reservations are strongly suggested casual dining attire</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Bianca's%20Ristorante?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-23-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/05/48/b8/85/bianca-s-ristorante-italiano.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>This Place is Temporarily Closed. Buona Salute, Good Health! At Bianca's Ristorante, nothing makes us happier than bringing people together through the warmth, comfort, and flavor of homemade Italian cuisine. With years of culinary experience passed down through our family and influences from the dishes of our home country, we transport you from North Fort Myers to the very streets of Italy. Our meals are always freshly prepared with only the best ingredients, and our warm, welcoming staff is here to ensure you feel right at home with us. Join us soon, indulge in fresh, familiar, delicious meals with friends and family, and let us share with you our love of all things food and hospitality.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Prawnbroker%20Restaurant%20and%20Fish%20Market?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-24-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/02/d3/9f/16/prawnbroker-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Walking through the front doors, guests are greeted by the in-house seafood market, where the Prawnbroker showcases their specially chosen fresh fillets of fish and beef, hand-cut on premise, that are sure to tempt the palates of all. To emphasize their commitment to buying local and bringing you the freshest seafood Ft. Myers has to offer, you'll find our hand picked selection straight from the local waters of the Gulf of Mexico. Here you'll get a peek at the sumptuous fare that you'll soon be enjoying from their comfortable yet elegant dining room. Feast your eyes on mouth-watering Snapper, Gulf Shrimp, Softshell Crabs, Mahi Mahi, and the best Grouper Florida has to offer. Small tubs of pale pink creamy shrimp bisque stand in line next to bases for both kinds of chowder - New England style being what the restaurant is most famous for, a nod to the original owners' home region. Diners consistently return to enjoy these favorites plus the greatest Florida Stone crabs (in season) and Maine Lobsters.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Island%20Pho%20%20Grill?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-25-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0d/dc/64/85/island-pho-and-grill.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Welcome to Island Pho  Grill, a place to call your own. Island Pho  Grill - Authentic Vietnamese cuisine. Delight your taste buds with a fresh homemade foods that take your senses away. Located in Matlacha, FL, we have a scrumptious menu, whether for lunch or dinner and we also offer catering services for your next event. Please contact us for more information.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Sakura%20Japanese%20Steak%20House%20%20Sushi%20Bar?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-26-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0a/5c/10/07/sushi.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Cape Coral Japanese Steak House and Sushi Bar. Where VIP's can eat for free. Get VIP status on our website (it's free) We serve Hibachi Steak, chicken, fish, shrimp, lobster table side with our master Japanese Hibachi chefs (we are told they are pretty funny too!). Dine at our Sushi bar with master sushi chef's preparing all your favorites and some of the most delectable sushi rolls you may have never tried before. Our House specialty is our famous "FAT GIRL ROLL". What's a Fat Girl, Check out our menu on our website, we personally guarantee you will love it! We now feature the largest Sake Bar in all of S.W. Florida. Enjoy your sushi the way it was meant to be by pairing it with an exotic Sake selection. Come visit us and bring lots of friends, it's more fun that way!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Old%20Fish%20House%20Marina?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-27-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/21/5f/3e/20/olde-fish-house-marina.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We're Olde Fish House Marina, and we've been a family owned and operated restaurant and seafood market here in Matlacha, FL, since 2011. Our goal is to bring our customers the best in fresh, local seafood from our docks to your table, including grouper, snapper, shrimp, and much more. We offer convenient dock access for anyone who would like a quick stop on their way in or out of the marina. We also offer kayak, canoe, and boat slip rentals so you can enjoy your day with us! Our ultimate goal is to support our local commercial fishermen to the best of our ability and our local artists in our gift shop and art gallery. We’re looking forward to partnering with Pine Island, Cape Coral, and Fort Myers consumers to keep the old Florida feel while supporting our locals. We’d like to personally invite you to stop by for one of our Po' Boy sandwiches, today!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Chicago%20Pizza?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-28-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/46/18/7a/come-on-in.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A Casual fun place to gather with friends and family. We specialize in thin crust and Deep Dish Chicago style pizzas, Italian Beef Sandwiches, All Vienna Beef Chicago Dogs and Tamales. All fresh, Every Day. We feature Fontanini Sausages and Meatballs. Chicago Pizza is a family owned and operated restaurant that has been in Cape Coral for over 20 years. The recipes originated in South Bridgeport and our customers agree that if you are from Chicago the food tastes like home and if you are not, it just tastes great! Great place to watch Chicago Sports.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Mexico%20Lindo%20Restaurant?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-29-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0d/4e/a6/f2/mexico-lindo-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>this is a family restaurant made it with our heart for you, a destination place in cape coral,Fl. with unique authentic and classic furniture from Jalisco Mexico, Great Food,the best Margaritas and Profesional Service. Full Bar service available, come and try our Flaming Coffee and Mango 3leches cake after your table side guacamole and Mar y Tierra Fajitas...will be our pleasure serve you</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Point%2057%20Kitchen%20%20Cocktails?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-30-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/12/d3/67/40/craft-cocktails.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Southern Coastal cuisine in the heart of Cape Coral Florida. We concentrate on fresh local ingredients and locally sourced Florida seafood, produce, and Florida craft beer.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Maria's%20Pizzeria%20%20Restaurant?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-31-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0b/63/b8/d8/maria-s-pizzeria-and.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Be transported to Old World Italy with our authentic family recipes at Maria's Pizzeria  Restaurant.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Miceli's%20Restaurant?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-32-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1a/55/ef/d3/new-tiki.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Casual dining, fun atmosphere, outdoor seating, live entertainment 7 days a week.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Nomiki's%20Plakka%20Greek%20Restaurant?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-35-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/07/a1/4a/49/nomiki-s-plakka-greek.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located at 12901-3 McGregor Blvd in Bridge Plaza (right next door to Dollar General and across the street from The Landings), is your best choice for Greek Food, especially in the Southwest Florida area. Our authentic menu and restaurant decorations allow for our customers to feel like they are sitting in a restuarant in Greece, enjoying an amazing traditional meal. Our homemade meals extend from appetizers such as Tiropitas, Saganaki- "The Flaming Cheese", a range of dips including Hummus and Tzatziki, to our Greek Salads with our very own dressing, to sandwiches like Gyros, Souvlakia, Loukaniko, to Entrees like Dolmathes, Rack of Lamb, Pastisio, and Mousaka, just to name a few. After dinner you can enjoy one of our many homemade desserts including Baklava, Rice Pudding, Galahktobouriko, and Kourourakia. Come dine in or call for take out! Hope to see you soon! OPA! To stay up to date on our Specials and Belly Dancer performances, 'Like' us on Facebook</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Ford's%20Garage?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-37-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0b/1b/4a/0e/photo1jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Ford's Garage Cape Coral is your top pit stop for the most delicious prime burgers, comfort food and delectable deserts. Conveniently located just west of Del Prado Blvd S before you hit the Cape Coral Bridge.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Cafe%20YOU?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-40-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0c/77/da/58/cafe-you.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Cafe YOU is an Australian Style Cafe` where you can enjoy authentic espresso coffee paired with fresh natural food including many Vegan  GF options.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Colleonis%20Ristorante%20Italiano?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-42-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/21/86/9b/99/colleoni-s-in-the-evening.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Directly from Italy, COLLEONI'S is a family operated Restaurant and Bakery featuring delicious Italian cuisine, friendly service and warm hospitality. We serve only authentic Italian food cooked in the Italian style, with fresh ingredients, with passion and love.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/10%20Twenty%20Five?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-43-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0d/34/d6/0f/dine.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>10 Twenty Five is family owned and operated in Cape Coral, FL. We feature craft beers, wine  scratch kitchen style pub food. Follow our Instagram @cape10twentyfive</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Bert's%20Bar%20%20Seafood%20Grill?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-47-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/08/0f/09/c3/coole-location-mit-flair.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>75 year oldtime Waterfront Restaurant and Bar with a Million Dollar view. Local seafood. Both local and national entertainment with no cover charge. Recommended by Southern Living, Coastal Living, Florida Travel  Life, Boston Globe, and American Airlines to mention a few. Quality food at reasonable prices. Great place to relax, enjoy the view and perhaps to see dolphins and/or manatees.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/CRaVE?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-48-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0e/d3/b2/d4/crave.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>CRaVE IS A LOCAL FAMILY OWNED RESTAURANT. FOR THE PAST 10 YEARS OUR CRaVE FAMILY HAS USED THE FINEST AND FRESHEST PRODUCTS . FARM FRESH EGGS, LOCAL GULF SHRIMP  FISH, LOCAL FARM FRUITS  VEGETABLES. WE BAKE OUR OWN BREADS, SMOKE AND ROAST OUR MEATS, CURE AND SMOKE OUR OWN BACON  SAUSAGES AND SO MUCH MORE! ALL FOOD IS COOKED TO ORDER, NOTHING IS PRE–CUT OR PRE-MADE SO PLEASE GIVE OUR CHEFS TIME TO COOK IT. YOU WONT JUST TASTE THE DIFFERENCE...YOU WILL CRaVE IT!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/First%20Watch?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-49-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/03/ce/6a/fd/first-watch-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>First Watch specializes in delicious creations freshly-prepared to order. Their fresh, award-winning Breakfast, Brunch and Lunch dishes are made using only the best ingredients without the use of heat lamps or deep fryers. The best part is their creative menu features traditional favorites like omelets, pancakes, salads and sandwiches.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Monarca's%20Authentic%20Mexican%20Cuisine%20Bar%20%20Grill?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-51-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/11/76/ec/72/monarcas.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>When you walk through our doors, you feel like you were suddenly transported to Mexico. Our food is fresh made out of the freshest ingredients and encompasses truly authentic dishes brought over from our family recipies in Mexico. The scent alone makes your mouth water. We are right on the water, with direct access to the river so you can come by boat, you can drive or you can walk because we are just two blocks north from the main downtown area strip street of Cape Coral Parkway on Del Prado Blvd. You will leave Monarca's but Monarca's will never leave you and you will keep coming for more!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Paradise%20Pizza%20of%20Cape%20Coral?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-54-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/79/a9/28/filename-888-jpg-thumbnail0.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Low-key Pizza Parlor: sit-down, carry out or delivery!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Duffy's%20Sports%20Grill?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-55-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/09/12/92/96/duffy-s-sports-grill.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Food you love in a casual dining, sports-themed experience. With locations throughout Florida, you are sure to have one nearby. Eat. Drink. Earn free meals. Enjoy all the perks of being an MVP! At Duffy's, Our Game Is Always On.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/The%20Melting%20Pot?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-56-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0c/e5/09/0b/20160908-225337-largejpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Our dining takes standard dinner experiences and flips them on their head. Interactive, hands-on cooking has no equal when you want to connect with family members or newly kindled friendships. Treat your one-and-only to a spontaneous romantic date or stop in to satisfy your cravings for delectable fondue.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/The%20O%20Bar?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-57-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/09/03/c0/44/the-o-bar.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The "O" Bar serves up low drink prices, dinner specials, entertainment, and great events that is now open to the public! We have awesome weekly meal specials (like $5 Steak Night every Thursday!), great entertainment (Live Bands every Friday Night!), and killer drink specials that are sure to please! Stop in today to check out The "O" and become a regular!!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Monkey%20Bar%20Steak%20%20Seafood?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-58-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0c/dc/88/0b/ladies-night-menus.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Very Casual outside and classy and formal inside! Happy Hour 7days a week from open until 8pm. Live music 7 days a week. Best Steak, Seafood, Burgers, Paninis  Appetizers in Cape Coral.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Iguana%20Mia%20of%20Cape%20Coral?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-59-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/10/21/4c/d7/monday-2-margaritas.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Iguana Mia Mexican Restaurant serving great Mexican food and Margaritas to Southwest Florida since 1990!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Hart%20%20Soul%20Cafe%20(%20Cape%20Coral%20)?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-60-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1d/af/1a/96/hart-soul-cafe-cape-coral.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The HART of our restaurant is in each of our customer's feeling like they are at home in the comfort of a clean and welcoming family atmosphere enjoying excellent food. The SOUL of our restaurant is the passion in each of our recipes prepared with great ingredients. please enjoy your meal. Nicolas  Bruna</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/FINS%20Seafood%20%20Dive%20Bar?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-62-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0e/83/fa/a4/seafood-enchiladas-and.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Welcome to FINS Seafood  Dive Bar: Cape Coral’s hotspot for fresh, fun, funky, Florida-style eats and drinks. Around here, we’re all about having good times with good people. We keep things casual and laid-back, just like life here in the Sunshine State. We’re known for our always fresh, locally sourced seafood, like our shrimp and scallop ceviche and our house fish and chips. Not that into seafood, you say? No problem -- with Philly cheesesteaks, salads, and a classic NY strip, no appetite will go unsatisfied. Grab a cold brew or a sweet cocktail, and you’re good to go. Whether you’re a local or a visitor, we can’t wait to have you stop by. Just remember the dress code: T-shirts, flip flops, and a smile.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Citrola's%20Italian%20Grill%20%20Pizzeria?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-65-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/06/40/04/12/citrola-s-italian-grill.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Our family has been serving award-winning Italian cuisine and pizza for over 20 years. Come find out why locals and snowbirds alike love our delicious food, great service and friendly atmosphere.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Leone%20Italian%20Food%20Specialty?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-66-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0d/ba/6e/07/pizza.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>This is a small Italian deli and specialty shop which is off the beaten path but the food is fantastic and like homemade. They also serve excellent Pizza and subs at lunch and going there is like visiting a small Italian deli in the cities of the Northeast</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Hooked%20Island%20Grill?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-67-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/16/34/84/55/hooked-island-grill-is.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Hooked Island Grill on Matlacha has the best waterfront views in the area. Enjoy one of the many fantastic menu items or chef specials daily. Watch the sunset from our covered deck area, which is actually over the water. Check our schedule for Live entertainment, featuring local sounds of the island. Not only will you enjoy our nightlife, but check out our local wildlife, dolphins, manatees, stingrays and an abundance of fish are seen in our waters every day. We are open 11 AM and kitchen closes at 9 PM. Sunday Breakfast Buffet  Bloody Mary Bar is served 9 AM to Noon. So whether you come for breakfast, lunch, or dinner, or just drinks on the rail watching an amazing sunset, you'll love Hooked Island Grill on Matlacha.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Paradise%20Deli%20%20Grill?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-68-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/06/01/1b/e6/paradise-deli-market.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Paradise Deli is located in beautiful Cape Coral, Florida at The Shops at Surfside. We serve Breakfast, Lunch  Dinner, 7 days a week. We are known throughout Southwest Florida for our award-winning Reuben sandwiches and our always fresh, always changing nightly specials. The Truth Is In The Taste Our menu is built around the idea that fresh ingredients and homemade food just taste better. Let Paradise Cater Your Next Event Have your next banquet, luncheon, party with us! If we can do it - WE WILL!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Aji%20Limon%20Peruvian%20Restaurant?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-69-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/05/a8/a4/4f/beef-with-rice-and-french.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Free WI-FI</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Ristorante%20Fabio%20Italian%20Restaurant?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-70-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/07/07/a4/5e/fabio-ristorante.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Ristorante Fabio is the latest in the legacy of Edmondo’s restaurants in New York. Edmondo Ciminati and his wife Tina began their venture in the early 70’s when they opened up Edmondo’s Seafood restaurant in Throggs Neck, New York. Along with their children, Isabella, Mirella, Viviana and Fabio, they owned and operated many other restaurants, including Edmondo’s Italian Seafood restaurant in Eastchester, Sig. Edmondo’s on the east side of Manhattan, Edmondo’s in the Bronx and Edmondo’s Too in White Plains. In the summer of 1993 Edmondo and Tina decided to sell the restaurants and head to Florida. On Dec. 13, 1993 they opened Ristorante Fabio. After 20 wonderful years, Edmondo and Tina have passed their business onto their daughter Viviana. As of January 2014, she has become owner and chef. She has worked with her father Edmondo since the age of 13, and has cherished all that she has learned from him. It is with much pride that she can continue their legacy.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Metro%20Diner?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-71-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/12/c5/ae/0d/blt-with-fries.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Local diner chain serving classic American breakfast, lunch and dinner in a warm atmosphere.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Keke's%20Breakfast%20Cafe?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-72-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/15/a5/01/67/waffel.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Keke’s Breakfast Cafe is dedicated to providing an outstanding breakfast; a meal where everything is handmade, using the best ingredients available, with fresh fruits and vegetables that are delivered daily, and using fresh bread and dairy products.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/First%20Round%20Draft%20Sports%20Bar%20%20Grille?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-74-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/b1/cc/58/filename-900-1353-jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>FAMILY OWNED AND OPERATED Our inviting neighborhood atmosphere, full-service bar and open layout appeals to sports fans and families alike. Our full-service waterfront patio includes boat dockage on the Honolulu Canal. Menu Variety A menu filled with bold-flavored, made-to-order items features Appetizers, a Kids Menu, Specialty Salads, Burgers, Deli Sandwiches, Wraps, Pastas, Seafood and Steak. Happy Hour Drink Specials 11am-6pm, Monday through Friday. Wide Screen TV's Throughout With over 30 wide screen TV's complemented by comfortable lounge chair seating, you never have to miss a moment of the game. Private TV speakers are also available so you can listen at your table to the TV of your choice! We Sell Gift Certificates!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Back%20Streets%20Sports%20Bar?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-75-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0d/df/b7/fb/facade-and-courtesy-limousine.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>BackStreets Sports Bar provides great food, drinks and daily entertainment in Cape Coral, FL.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Outback%20Steakhouse?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-76-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/03/06/67/f3/outback-steakhouse.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Outback Steakhouse, the home of juicy steaks, spirited drinks and Aussie hospitality. Find our location in Cape Coral on Pine Island Road and Del Prado Blvd across from Lowes and Publix.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Caffe%20Toscano?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-77-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/12/5a/f7/a0/dine.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A truly unique Italian fine dining experience. Chef/owner Antonio brings Tuscany to Fort Myers with an array of imported Italian products, the best extra virgin olive oil, the finest ingredients and specials that change weekly. We are temporarily closed and will reopen in October 2022.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/BIG8%20BBQ?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-78-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/1d/1b/11/43/ribs-bone-in-ribs-beautifully.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Here at Big8 BBQ, our mission is simple: To provide the best quality BBQ and service we can. We achieve this by meticulously preparing our smoked meats and taking a customer-first approach to all aspects of our restaurant. ​ Big8 BBQ opened its doors on October 29th 2020 in Downtown Cape Coral. Our unique restaurant layout allows hungry visitors to either quickly order food at our quick service counter or or sit back in our full-service dining area and enjoy an authentic BBQ restaurant experience. ​ Our full liquor bar serves signature cocktails that are hand-crafted using locally sourced spirits by Mr. Tom's Spirits. ​ We source our food locally and sustainably ensuring our guests have the best tasting product imaginable.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Moretti%20Cucina%20Italians?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-79-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1c/9b/16/d0/spaghetti-carbonara.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Serving delicious pasta  other authentic Italian dishes in Cape Coral</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/South%20Cape%20Diner?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-80-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/05/0e/1b/85/south-cape-diner.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Breakfast and lunch - they are on Facebook</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Thai%20Nawa%20Cuisine?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-82-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/07/03/66/b8/getlstd-property-photo.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Thai Nawa Cuisine is a casual dine-in and take-out restaurant in Cape Coral, Florida offering authentic and contemporary Thai cuisine prepared fresh in the restaurant.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Denny's?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-84-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/05/06/ef/7a/denny-s.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>For more than 65 years, Denny's has been bringing people together over great food. It's the place where people can relax and be themselves while enjoying classic American comfort food and everyday value. Whether it's appetizers, breakfast, lunch or dinner, we pride ourselves in serving our guests the diner food they love including favorites like Moons Over My Hammy®, Sizzlin' Skillets, hand-dipped Milk Shakes, 100% Beef Burgers and the world-famous Build Your Own Grand Slam®. And now, you can bring the diner home by ordering diner classics or one our Family Packs. See you at Denny's.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Azucar%20Restaurant%20and%20Bakery?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-86-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/06/27/6a/d4/azucar-restaurant-and.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>This is a wonderful, family owned little reaStay rant and bakery. We have eaten there many times - breakfast, lunch and dinner. This restaurant should be included in your listings. The food is authentic and delicious. The service is great. Love this place!!!!!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/The%20Omelet%20Shop?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-87-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/13/86/e9/20/western.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>This is a breakfast/lunch eatery.It offers american style food</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Rusty's%20Raw%20Bar%20and%20Grill%20-%20Cape%20Coral?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-88-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/11/ff/a1/61/our-outdoor-patio.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Rusty's Raw Bar  Grill is a laid back and local spot with four locations in Cape Coral, Estero, Fort Myers, and Naples. We offer a casual dining experience and welcoming staff. Enjoy live entertainment, daily drink deals, and a wide variety of menu items including fresh seafood and hot-off-the-grill dishes. Rusty's has something to satisfy everyone's taste buds.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Carrabba's%20Italian%20Grill?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-89-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/b5/db/fe/carrabba-s-italian-grill.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Enjoy authentic Italian for dine-in, carryout, delivery or catering.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Olive%20Garden%20Italian%20Restaurant?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-96-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/02/ce/a6/c4/front-of-olive-garden.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>All of your favorites are just a few clicks away! View our menu online and Order Now for convenient Carside Delivery or come in for our famous never-ending first course of freshly baked breadsticks and your choice of homemade soup or garden fresh salad. Enjoy abundant portions of classic Italian favorites the whole family craves like the Tour of Italy, our irresistible Chicken Parmigiana, or everyone's favorite Fettuccine Alfredo, made fresh from our kitchen to your table. Gather together with the people you love over a meal worth sharing at Olive Garden. We're all family here.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Bob%20Evans?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-100-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0e/99/2a/62/cobb-salad-just-look.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Welcome to the home of America's Farm Fresh! Enjoy our all-day menu featuring signature breakfasts, NEW Banana Nut Hotcakes and homestyle Family Meals to Go at your Bob Evans in Cape Coral. Order online for curbside pickup or delivery (where available). Download the farm!🚜 Ordering your homestyle favorites from Bob Evans has gotten easier than ever before. Save your favorite orders, pay using your phone when you dine-in, get exclusive offers and more with Bob Evans mobile app.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Stillwater%20Grille?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-104-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/04/12/51/1f/stillwater-grille.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Stillwater Grille is located on the corner of McGregor and Cypress Lake in Fort Myers. We are a family owned business. Stillwater Grille is owned by people who have a passion for great craft beers, fine wines and wonderful all-natural food. We love to eat, drink and have fun. We have three dining areas-outside on our gorgeous patio, in the bar area and in our fine dining room. Come check us out today!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Lelulo's%20Pizzeria?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-105-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/cf/dc/bf/cheesy-goodness.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Lelulo's "Pizza Life" has over 20 years of experience in the restaurant industry and offers a full menu of specialty pizzas and subs. All dough is homemade with fresh ingredients and baked in our brick oven! You will have your choice of sauce and all pizzas are baked to a perfect, crispy finish. The owners of Lelulo's "Pizza Life" are active volunteers in the community and believe in giving back. They support children's activities, local schools, and churches throughout the community.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Perk%20%20Brew?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-106-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0f/bb/17/1b/special-occasion-ask.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Perk  Brew is voted a local favorite by the Cape Coral community. Great coffee shop cafe that offers coffee, beer, wine and good eats! Open for breakfast and lunch. Stop by Thursday nights for Open Mic Night.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/The%20Go%20Go%20Diner?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-107-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0f/a4/62/63/build-your-own-omelet.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Culinary Institute of America graduate whipping up South West Florida's BEST Corned Beef Hash made from scratch...Old school diner feel served Southern Style. The good 'ole boys dig our home-made Sausage Gravy 'cuz we use damn good sausage 'n plenty of it. Corned Beef Hash, Biscuits 'n Gravy, Red Velvet Pancakes, or the juiciest Burger you ever did have...at the gogo diner!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Everybody's%20Brunch%20Place?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-108-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0d/ae/9d/6a/2-eggs-2-sausage-grits.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>7</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Luciano's%20Pizza?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-112-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0f/1e/21/92/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Luciano's Pizza is currently located at 728 SW Pine island Rd, Cape Coral, FL 33991. Order your favorite pizza, pasta, salad, and more, all with the click of a button. Luciano's Pizza accepts orders online for pickup and delivery.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Chen's%20China%20Bistro?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-114-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/07/4a/ff/c8/chen-s-china-bistro.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Chen's China Bistro serves New York Style Chinese food. Our restaurant is the perfect place for a romantic dinner, celebrating a birthday with a loved one, or a fun night out with friends. Also we have beer and wine, bubble tea available</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Wingnuts?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-115-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/03/e7/45/c4/wingnuts.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We are locate in the Moderna Plaza just south of Hancock Bridge Pkwy and north of CC hospital. Prettiest bldg. on the Cape..... We offer FREE foosball and air hockey for all.Also come see and get your picture with our famous Leg lamp from what movie ???</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Grandma%20Penny's%20Pizza?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-116-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/21/96/21/6e/grandma-penny-s-pizza.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Grandma Penny’s Pizza, Fort Myers pizza restaurant offers a truly Italian experience using centuries-old techniques and authentic handmade ingredients! Offering NY Style Brick Oven Pizzas, Pasta Dinners, Fresh Subs, Salads, Calzones, Stromboli, Beer, Wine, and more! Located at the former Amore Brick Oven Pizza location, we serve oven-fresh creations brimming with the cheesy and tangy goodness people have come to love, plus a few more flavors to spice things up! Our signature pizza sauce, which we have perfected using the finest ingredients and spices, is sure to add delight to every diner’s pizza experience.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Nestor's%20Restaurant?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-117-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/17/ba/ca/ff/grilled-chicken-breast.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Homestyle cooking, everything cooked fresh on premises, family owned  operated!!!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Habaneros%20Mexican%20Grill?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-118-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/21/d6/b5/74/our-logo-we-are-located.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Habaneros Mexican Grill is a Mexican Restaurant located in North Fort Myers, FL. We do not only specialize in Authentic Mexican Food but we also provide high-quality customer service to each one of our customers. Here we love to make you feel welcome.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Sonny's%20BBQ?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-119-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0b/b0/22/31/sonny-s-bbq.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Sonny's BBQ of Fort Myers. Southern BBQ at its finest. Slow-smoking favorites like pulled pork, ribs, brisket since 1968.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Crisp%20Creperie?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-120-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/19/57/bf/8e/blondie-fresh-bananas.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Savory and Sweet gourmet crêpes handmade with love! We also offer appetizers, vegetarian options, and beer and wine.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/CapeCoral/Gulyas%20Factory?-CapeCoral-Restaurants-121-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/23/33/5a/bd/entrance-gulyas-factory.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located in the heart of Cape Coral, we serve delicious meals and homemade dishes made from fresh and healthy ingredients for breakfast, lunch  dinner. Our menu includes typical Hungarian dishes, Wiener Schnitzel, cold drinks, coffee, beer and wine. And if you want to eat at home or host an event, our team will be happy to help you. You can also order take-away to eat our delicous dishes at your home.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

</urlset>