<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1">
<script async="false" type="text/javascript" src="chrome-extension://fnjhmkhhmkbjkkabndcnnogagogbneec/in-page.js"/>
<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Edison%20and%20Ford%20Winter%20Estates?-FortMyers-Attractions-1-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/06/bb/aa/0f/edison-ford-winter-estates.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Visitors to the Edison and Ford Winter Estates in Fort Myers will enjoy seeing the winter residences of famous inventors Thomas Edison and Henry Ford. There are historical buildings, award-winning gardens, the Edison Botanic Research Lab and the Inventions Museum. The museum has hundreds of inventions, artifacts and special exhibits. Edison Ford offers many tour options, including special "Inside-the-Homes" and "Inside-the-Lab" Tours on select days. The audio tour is available in English, Spanish, German and French. Historian led tours are also offered in German on select days. Group tours can be arranged in advance.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Six%20Mile%20Cypress%20Slough%20Preserve?-FortMyers-Attractions-2-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/05/b8/9a/35/six-mile-cypress-slough.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Six Mile Cypress Slough Preserve is a 3,500 acre wetland, located in Fort Myers, Florida, which filters rainwater on its way towards Estero Bay. The preserve contains a 1.2-mile boardwalk trail, interpretive center, and amphitheater.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Fort%20Myers%20River%20District?-FortMyers-Attractions-3-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/05/71/04/c2/fort-myers-river-district.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Downtown Fort Myers offers a variety of restaurants, cocktails, and nightlife for any appetite and scene you are seeking…..from outdoor dining, rooftop drinks, and spectacular sunsets; a variety of cuisines and spirits await you/</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/McGregor%20Boulevard?-FortMyers-Attractions-4-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/05/3c/cf/a3/palms-on-either-side.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>McGregorBoulevard is a lovely street in Fort Myers. It is lined on both sides with royal palms.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/IMAG%20History%20%20Science%20Center?-FortMyers-Attractions-5-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/03/c6/51/84/imaginarium-hands-on.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Touch live sea life, engineer a creation, run through a rainstorm! Your admission package to IMAG provides hours of fun and entertainment for the entire family. Offering over 60 interactive exhibits, there is fun for the entire family to explore science, technology, engineering, and math (STEM), and the history of Southwest Florida. You will enjoy touching live marine animals in our Sea to See Touch Tanks; a 3,200-gallon aquarium displaying a variety of fish, including sharks; our Living Lab with turtles, a ball python, frogs, a bearded dragon, prairie dogs and more; daily LIVE! Animal Encounters; the opportunity to become a TV weather forecaster in our mini-studio; a walk through Southwest Florida in our Hall of History; a 3-D movie, and so much more! A visit to IMAG nurtures intellectual curiosity, discovery, and innovation.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Fleamasters%20Fleamarket?-FortMyers-Attractions-6-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/05/fa/f5/a0/fleamasters-fleamarket.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Let's go shopping! Treat yourself to Fleamaster's festive atmosphere, pick up a week's supply of fresh produce, and stroll through the hundreds of bargain-packed booths. Along every aisle, you'll discover small owner-operated shops that specialize in unique items - an eclectic mix of new and old - arts and crafts, antiques and collectibles, and lots more. Kitchen products, clothing and shoes, luggage, jewelry and watches, 20 snack bars serving yummy treats. Name it, it's here! Find gifts for your family and friends and something just for you.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Florida%20Repertory%20Theatre?-FortMyers-Attractions-7-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/03/7c/b7/e9/florida-repertory-theatre.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Florida Repertory Theatre performs in the Historic Arcade Theatre in the heart of the Fort Myers River District.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Edison%20Park?-FortMyers-Attractions-8-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/15/31/07/70/parc-cote-villa-ford.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The grounds of Edison Park and the Edison/Ford homes are beautiful from the banks of the Caloosahatchee River across McGregor Blvd to the champion Banyan Tree by Edison's laboratory.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Butterfly%20Estates?-FortMyers-Attractions-9-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/2b/b8/51/butterfly-estates.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Home of The Florida Native Butterfly Society Conservatory. A non profit organization dedicate to protecting, preserving and populating Florida's Native Butterflies! Visit our Bookstore and gift shop.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/List%20Distillery?-FortMyers-Attractions-10-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/15/08/a1/a1/img-20181013-145742-107.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>List Distillery is a Family Owned and Operated Craft Spirit Distillery founded in 2015 and located in Fort Myers, Florida. Renate and Thomas List are passionate people devoted to the art of distilling the best craft spirits possible using locally sourced crops and organic ingredients. Working side by side, in their state of the art distillery, Renate and Thomas combine their passion and knowledge of old world craft distilling with innovative ideas to produce unique flavors and memorable experiences. To Renate and Thomas, “Craft Distilling is the art of combining our love, knowledge, local ingredients, creativity and the ability to dream!” Stop by the List Distillery and watch as they Mash, Cook, Mix and Distill unique flavors such as Apple Pie Rum, Key Lime Pie Rum, Habanero Honey Whiskey, Ginger Lime Gin, Hazelnut Liqueur and Caffe Latte. Don’t forget to stop by the tasting room as well to get a true taste for Mr. Tom’s Spirits.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Centennial%20Park?-FortMyers-Attractions-11-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/09/e2/6d/5a/centennial-park.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located on the Caloosahatchee River and connected to downtown Ft. Myers, This nice little park is a great place to relax.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Edison%20Mall?-FortMyers-Attractions-12-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/13/5d/a9/de/20180620-113324-largejpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Visit Edison Mall to shop your favorite stores, enjoy a meal at one of their many restaurants or enjoy entertainment for the entire family.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Calusa%20Nature%20Center%20and%20Planetarium?-FortMyers-Attractions-13-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/15/d9/e5/bd/our-beautiful-pine-flatlands.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Our 105-acre facility hosts a true Florida swamp and we house injured native wildlife that may never be released into the wild. We also have exotic and exotic invasive species found or surrendered by owners. Daily animal demos! Special topics talks weekly (All about Alligators, Eyes on Eagles, Butterflies, Solar Observing on Fridays at the Planetarium). We have a cool planetarium (44-foot dome with a Media Globe II planetarium projection system) with three different shows per day and different shows each month. There are special events throughout the year. Check out our classes starting up in 2018!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/North%20Shore%20Park?-FortMyers-Attractions-14-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/16/5d/e3/06/photo1jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Low-key park area by the river featuring picnic pavilions  a pier for fishing enthusiasts.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Sidney%20%20Berne%20Davis%20Art%20Center?-FortMyers-Attractions-15-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/09/31/10/02/sidney-berne-davis-art.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Sidney  Berne Davis Art Center, run by Florida Arts, Inc. (a 501c3 organization), is a must-see attraction with a colorful history. The center is dedicated to bringing world-class art events to the Southwest Florida community. Within our restored, state-of-the-art facility, we present a wide range of events to the public. From concerts to art exhibitions, galas to lectures, and providing educational arts experiences for children and adults alike– we promise excellence! Florida Arts, Inc. nurtures innovation and excellence in the visual and performing arts via exhibitions, performances, education, and community outreach. Through our development and management of the Sidney and Berne Davis Art Center, we carry on the legacy of Berne Davis and her mission to provide a world-class venue and open access to the arts for all Members of the Southwest Florida Community.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Southern%20Fresh%20Farms?-FortMyers-Attractions-16-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0e/1b/a7/7d/southern-fresh.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Come get the freshest produce, fresh cut flowers, take a stroll to see in their hydroponic operation on your way to visit the barnyard animals. Your kids will love their huge playground and you can sit and relax by the waterfall on a swing.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Florida%20Native%20Butterfly%20Society?-FortMyers-Attractions-17-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/11/93/7e/f9/20171220-123318-largejpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Our educational coervatory is the only facility of its kind that is dedicated to safeguard of our incredible and diverse native butterflies of Southwest Florida. Our primary goal is to educate our guests on the importance of building butterfly habitats and protecting our natural environment where ever they may reside.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Coastal%20Dayz%20Brewery?-FortMyers-Attractions-18-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/14/3d/2a/5f/beer.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>With 16 tapz, we’ve got our staples like Wannabe Blonde, Seaz The Day IPA and Pirate’s Porter, and regularly feature a few specialty and guest tapz also. Inside the brewery, you’ll find friendly faces and a chill atmosphere while you enjoy one of our beer flights. Outside, you can relax under an umbrella on the patio and watch the world go by as you and your favorite people (and pets) spend the day or night in our downtown paradise. We regularly have food vendors serving inside the brewery (see coastaldayzbrewery.com for info) and you can also bring your own food in or have some delivered. Unfortunately, due to our limited size, layout, and chill atmosphere, we are unable to provide space or entertainment for children.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Burroughs%20Home%20%20Gardens?-FortMyers-Attractions-19-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/01/53/e6/58/burroughs-home.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Built in 1901, this Georgian Revival Mansion was the scene of many social events that hosted the Fort Myers' elite. Antique furnishings, historical artifacts and delightful tales of growing up as the privileged daughters of Nelson  Adeline Burroughs, and so much more await visitors who want to take a step back in time. Guided Historical Tours are conducted by reservation only. Please contact venue for details. Parking is located across the street, behind the Langford-Kingston Home. (2500 First Street)</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Millennial%20Brewing%20%20Co?-FortMyers-Attractions-20-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/17/7b/0c/42/at-millennial-brewing.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Downtown Fort Myers’ largest microbrewery, Millennial Brewing Company was founded by two Millennial generation entrepreneurs seeking to escape their corporate desk jobs in the technology industry. Our “Beer for Good” philosophy has allowed us to contribute to more than 150 charities in our first four years in business. By hosting events, donating beer, brew alongs and large-scale fundraisers, Millennial Brewing Company has become one of Southwest Florida’s biggest supporters of local causes.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Alliance%20for%20the%20Arts?-FortMyers-Attractions-22-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/09/cc/f4/79/alliance-for-the-arts.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Alliance for the Arts is building community through arts in the heart of Fort Myers! The 10-acre campus features: a theater presenting more than 100 theatrical performances a year; an amphitheater for concerts and outdoor movies; art galleries; youth and adult education programs; a weekly Green Market and free yoga on Saturday mornings.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Another%20Time?-FortMyers-Attractions-25-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/19/84/fd/06/another-time-timeless.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Another Time is a unique art gallery, souvenir  gift shop in Fort Myers, FL featuring local artists creating Steampunk, Tropical, Whimsical  Old Florida painting, lamps, decor, jewelry  more. It is an addition to Timeless, also in the heart of The River District, and Island Visions, located in the vibrant art community of Matlacha, FL. On - Site artist Eliza, uses the skills  talents acquired as a professional jeweler of 30 years to create one of a kind “jewelry for the home”. Dubbed “the coolest shop” in Fort Myers, Another Time combines the feel of the tropics, the vintage  Victorian aesthetics of steampunk and the vibe of “Jules Verne” in a setting right out “20000 Leagues Under the Sea”. So set your Inter - Dimensional travel coordinates to Another Time to enjoy something not found just anywhere.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Caloosa%20Sound%20Convention%20Center%20%20Amphitheater?-FortMyers-Attractions-26-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1b/4d/e2/d5/caloosa-sound-convention.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Fueled by the energy of a bustling downtown and the river’s sense of discovery, Luminary Hotel's adjacent event center is completely managed by Luminary’s team. No third-party contracts or less than spectacular catering can be found here. Soaring ceilings, grand spaces and flexible configurations highlight the significant renovations and upgrades. The 30,000 square foot Caloosa Sound Ballroom with generous pre-function areas lends itself to showstopping general sessions, elegant receptions and convenient breakouts. To add a touch of drama, the outdoor amphitheater and park provides the perfect setting for a private concert, spontaneous team building or closing rally for your troops.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Fort%20Myers%20Skatium?-FortMyers-Attractions-32-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/18/1e/03/62/photo2jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Fort Myers Skatium offers an ice skating arena, an athletic gymnasium and a fitness center all under one roof. The Fort Myers Skatium operates Internal Skating Institute (ISI) and United States Figure Skating Association (USFSA) in it’s figure skating, certified ice and in-line hockey leagues, freestyle skating, and exciting birthday packages.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/The%20Forum?-FortMyers-Attractions-34-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://www.mallscenters.com/uploads/plans/the-forum-2830_thumb.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Outdoor center with Home Depot, Target, Bed Bath  Beyond  Staples, plus services  casual dining.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Murder%20Mystery%20Dinner%20Train?-FortMyers-Attractions-48-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/03/ce/87/0a/seminole-gulf-railway.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>All aboard the Murder Mystery Dinner Train for a one-of-a-kind theatrical and culinary experience! Enjoy a five-course dinner with a choice from three entrees, prepared fresh onboard the train while a live murder mystery show is played out in the dining cars during your forty-mile round trip over 3 and half hours from Colonial Station in Fort Myers, Florida.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Extreme%20Rage%20Paintball%20Park%20of%20Fort%20Myers?-FortMyers-Attractions-55-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/08/6c/6e/85/getlstd-property-photo.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Imagine How Much Fun It Will Be To Blast Your Friends With Paintballs! Extreme Rage Paintball Park Has Been Serving SWFL for Over 20 Years.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Fowler%20Firearms%20and%20Gun%20Range?-FortMyers-Attractions-63-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/07/3c/57/2c/fowler-firearms-gun-range.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Fowler Firearms and Gun Range SW Florida,s premier indoor shooting facility, offers the optimal environment for your shooting pleasure. We have 6 extra-wide shooting booths, double filter ventilation, and our range is fully air conditioned for your comfort. Each lane is viewable on our closed circuit television system. We offer our exclusive Try Before You Buy program, with over 100 firearms to try. This will ensure you're purchasing the firearm that suits you best. We have our Free Day for Ladies on Thursday, and Free Day for Men on Friday. Rifles and shotguns are allowed every day. Rifles up to, and including 308, shotguns with a full stock shooting 000 buck or slugs only. Our range is 25 yards.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Top%20Golf?-FortMyers-Attractions-64-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/22/ab/c4/48/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Top Golf is a sports entertainment complex that features an inclusive, high-tech golf game that everyone can enjoy. Paired with an outstanding food and beverage menu, climate-controlled hitting bays and music, every Topgolf has an energetic hum that you can feel right when you walk through the door.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Cornog%20Plaza?-FortMyers-Attractions-65-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/de/dd/a8/spring-2020.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Cornog Plaza is an open space located outside the Lee County Library. The plaza is named for June Cornog, a retired U.S. Navy commander.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Fort%20Myers:%20An%20Alternative%20History%20Mural?-FortMyers-Attractions-67-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1c/57/30/90/11-13-20.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located on the eastern face of the federal courthouse in the downtown Fort Myers River District is a 20 foot tall by 100 foot long ceramic tile mural.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Fort%20Myers%20Historical%20Marker?-FortMyers-Attractions-69-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/ee/0d/4f/historical-marker-on.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>This historical marker is in Downtown Fort Myers just off of main street. You could easily walk by unless you are looking for shops on the side streets. It commemorates the ancient Caloosa villages that were originally here and beginnings of the European occupation of the area. The marker talks about the building of the fort that was first named Fort Harvie, and would eventually be named Fort Myers in 1850.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Florida%20Panther%20Installation?-FortMyers-Attractions-70-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/e2/a1/0a/spring-2020.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Florida Panther is a 50-foot long installation that occupies the median on Monroe Street opposite the entrance to the Caloosa Sound Convention Center.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Buckingham%20%20Page%20Army%20Air%20Fields%20Monument?-FortMyers-Attractions-71-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/bc/c8/ef/feb-2020.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>It honors the airmen and others who trained during World War II at Fort Myers' air bases, Buckingham Field.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Tarpon%20Street%20Pier?-FortMyers-Attractions-73-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/bf/9b/47/tarpon-street-pier.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A 700' public access fishing pier over the Caloosahatchee River. Located at the north end of Tarpon Street off Palm Beach Blvd (Hwy 80). Parking is free.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/The%20Laboratory%20Theater?-FortMyers-Attractions-77-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0f/23/47/28/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Laboratory Theater of Florida began in 2008 as a dream of founders Annette Trossbach, Nicole Rizley, and Louise Wigglesworth. The theater began as a community theater with the goal of offering new and cutting edge plays that would expand the consciousness of the southwest Florida community and bring people together in the service of greater understanding, as well as regularly offering classics. </image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Florida%20Boxing%20Hall%20Of%20Fame%20Museum?-FortMyers-Attractions-96-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1d/77/61/97/entrance.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located in the same building but separate from the Internationally known SJC Boxing Gym.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Lakes%20Regional%20Park?-FortMyers-Attractions-100-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/10/57/83/54/playground.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Lakes Park encompasses nearly 300 acres of beautiful nature trails, lakes and gardens. Two playgrounds and water parks, a miniature train ride and railroad museum, bikes and watercraft available for rental, food concession, fitness trail and lots of picnicking areas. Every year over a million people enjoy Lakes Park's natural beauty for exercise and family recreation.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/JetBlue%20Park?-FortMyers-Attractions-101-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/12/34/88/1f/20180227-152744-largejpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>JetBlue Park is a baseball park in Fort Myers, Florida, part of the Fenway South training and development facility.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/CenturyLink%20Sports%20Complex%20-%20Hammond%20Stadium?-FortMyers-Attractions-102-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/07/82/1d/25/hammond-stadium.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Fort Myers Miracle are the Class A Advanced minor league baseball affiliate of the Minnesota Twins Major League Baseball club. Since moving to Fort Myers in 1992, the Miracle have qualified for the Florida State League Playoffs eight times and won the Florida State League Championship in 2014. Home games are played at Hammond Stadium at the CenturyLink Sports Complex. The Fort Myers Miracle season begins in April and ends in September.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Railroad%20Museum%20of%20South%20Florida?-FortMyers-Attractions-103-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/04/41/1b/f9/railroad-museum-of-south.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Railroad Museum of South Florida,Inc operates the Lakes Park and Gulf Railroad and Railroad Museum in Lakes Regional Park in south Ft Myers Florida. Lakes Regional Park is a Approx 300 Acres in size, and is part of the Lee County Parks and Recreation Dept of Lee County Florida. The property was originally an old rock quarry which has been reclaimed by Mother Nature and transformed into a waterfront wonderland for all of Florida's natural beauty! The Lakes Park and Gulf Railroad operates daily train rides along a 1 1/2 mile track which meanders around and between the many lakes, passing small villages and thru a tunnel. The Lakes Park Enrichment Foundation was created to monitor the over all future of the park.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Gannon's%20Antiques%20%20Art?-FortMyers-Attractions-104-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/02/93/53/e5/welcome-to-gannon-s-antiques.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Inside Gannon’s Antiques  Art they have over 100 unique vendors displaying their finest treasures in their 20,000 square foot indoor mall. their gallery has sold tens of thousands of fine pieces over the years to customers nationally  internationally. Celebrities frequently purchase from them, and our pieces can be found in the most amazing homes around the world.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Gulf%20Coast%20Town%20Center?-FortMyers-Attractions-105-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/05/49/c9/66/gulf-coast-town-center.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Gulf Coast Town Center features casual and upscale restaurants, as well as shopping that includes 20 anchor stores, 80 specialty shops and more than 30 eateries. After shopping, catch a movie at Regal Cinema.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/John%20Yarbrough%20Linear%20Park?-FortMyers-Attractions-107-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0b/b6/83/36/water-on-left-and-marsh.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>You’ll find the John Yarbrough Linear Park Trail to be an unexpected surprise in Fort Myers. Although bound by busy streets in all directions, the corridor itself is green and serene. The paved trail rolls alongside the Ten Mile Canal for 6 miles and crosses over it on a few pedestrian bridges where you can stop and take in the views. Look for egrets, herons, and other birds wading through its lush vegetation, and eagles in the tall treetops. You might even get lucky and spot an alligator.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Barbara%20B%20Mann%20Performing%20Arts%20Hall?-FortMyers-Attractions-108-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0c/3c/40/a8/rock-n-roll.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Barbara B. Mann Performing Arts Hall at FSW features the largest proscenium stage in Southwest Florida; and is a 1,874-seat facility that presents National Touring Broadway musicals such as: The Phantom of the Opera, Disney’s The Lion King, Les Misérables, WICKED, Jersey Boys, The Radio City Christmas Spectacular starring The Rockettes® and The Book of Mormon.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Suncoast%20Credit%20Union%20Arena?-FortMyers-Attractions-109-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/15/d0/a0/75/photo2jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Suncoast Credit Union Arena is a 75,000 sq ft multipurpose arena on the campus of Florida SouthWestern State College in Fort Myers, Florida. It is the home of the FSW Buccaneers men's and women's basketball and volleyball teams.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Alico%20Arena?-FortMyers-Attractions-110-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/12/e1/65/10/alico-arena-on-the-fgcu.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Alico Arena is a 120,000 sq ft multipurpose arena on the campus of Florida Gulf Coast University in Fort Myers, Florida. It is the home of the FGCU Eagles volleyball and men's and women's basketball teams. It holds 4,633 people in basketball configuration.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Wa-Ke%20Hatchee%20Recreation%20Center?-FortMyers-Attractions-111-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0a/b3/f7/06/photo1jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>County recreation space featuring 2 small lakes, walking trails, tennis courts  a dog park.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Florida%20Gulf%20Coast%20University%20Art%20Galleries?-FortMyers-Attractions-119-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0f/5f/8a/19/20th-annual-student-juried.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Exhibitions focus on contemporary art from local, national, and international artists as well as the faculty and students. The Art Galleries strive to offer diverse selections of mediums, content and culture while collaborating with other departments on campus to expand the scope of the visual arts.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/PopStroke?-FortMyers-Attractions-141-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1c/c1/81/13/two-18-hole-putting-courses.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Two 18-hole putting courses designed by Tiger Woods and TGR Design. Full-service restaurant, bar, and ice cream parlor.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/HeadPinz?-FortMyers-Attractions-144-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0f/eb/e5/1f/48-000-square-feet-of.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>HeadPinz Ft Myers is THE entertainment destination in SW FL. Great games, awesome food  beverages.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Regal%20Gulf%20Coast?-FortMyers-Attractions-147-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/15/79/54/11/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Regal, operates one of the largest and most geographically diverse theatre circuits in the United States. They believe that the size, reach and quality of the company's theatre circuit provides its patrons with a convenient and enjoyable movie-going experience. They are committed to being “The Best Place to Watch a Movie!”</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Art4wear.%20Art%20And%20Fashion?-FortMyers-Attractions-148-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/24/95/a2/c8/art-gallery.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Wearable art boutique and art gallery</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/University%20Village%20Shops%20%20Dining?-FortMyers-Attractions-152-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/1a/9c/6d/ed/restaurant-and-bar-options.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Whether an early workout or a cocktail after work, University Village Shops caters to your lifestyle, your needs any day or evening, breakfast, lunch and dinner.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Looking%20Glass%20Fort%20Myers?-FortMyers-Attractions-153-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1a/b7/14/e1/browsing-the-art-with.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Southwest Florida's first immersive art gallery presents 5 room-sized interactive installations that transports audiences of any age into a realm of imagination.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Fort%20Myers%20Mighty%20Mussels?-FortMyers-Attractions-154-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://img.mlbstatic.com/milb-images/image/upload/t_16x9/t_w1536/milb/mx21jyrdbridwmzadjck.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The Fort Myers Mighty Mussels are a Minor League Baseball team of the Florida State League and the Single-A affiliate of the Minnesota Twins.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Dave%20%20Buster's?-FortMyers-Attractions-157-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media.daveandbusters.com/media/5262/faces_14_455_r4-srgb.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Bring your friends and enjoy local and weekly specials. A fun experience for any occasion. Eat, drink, play and watch sports - all under one roof.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Castle%20Golf?-FortMyers-Attractions-158-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>http://www.castle-golf.com/images/top10image.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Medieval castle-themed mini-golf course amid waterfalls, tropical plants  other garden scenery.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Sky%20Zone%20Trampoline%20Park?-FortMyers-Attractions-159-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://d3qlyn3oeazit.cloudfront.net/production/ImageAsset/873/asset/square_640_1618244694-AirCourt.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Indoor trampoline park featuring freestyle bouncing, dodgeball, fitness programs  more.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Spinz?-FortMyers-Attractions-160-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://popmenucloud.com/cdn-cgi/image/width%3D960%2Cheight%3D960%2Cfit%3Dscale-down%2Cformat%3Dauto%2Cquality%3D60/ikwtavlj/a4671f29-5430-4e85-bbed-ea5523bf00bd.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>All-ages, old-school roller skating rink plus a cafe with casual chow along with beer  wine.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Sky%20Zone%20Trampoline%20Park%20at%20The%20Forum?-FortMyers-Attractions-161-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://d3qlyn3oeazit.cloudfront.net/production/ImageAsset/873/asset/square_640_1618244694-AirCourt.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Indoor trampoline park featuring freestyle bouncing, dodgeball, fitness programs  more.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/GameTime?-FortMyers-Attractions-162-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://dynamic-media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0a/0f/56/f2/gametime-fort-myers-mega.jpg?w=1600h=-1s=1</image:loc>

<image:title>GameTime Fort Myers is a 22,000 sqft. Entertainment Center located in the Gulf Coast Town Center. They offer fun indoor amusement with a full service experience in their beautiful Restaurant, full liquor Sports Bar and Mega Arcade including over 120 video games, simulators, prize machines and 6 lanes of mini bowling. It's fun for everyone and a great place to watch the game. Let them host and cater your next event, parties are their specialty!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Revolution%20Cable%20Park?-FortMyers-Attractions-163-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://dynamic-media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0a/0f/56/f2/gametime-fort-myers-mega.jpg?w=1600h=-1s=1</image:loc>

<image:title>Lake featuring overhead cables with ski ropes to pull wakeboarders  other water-sports enthusiasts.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Wisteria%20Tea%20Room%20%20Cafe?-FortMyers-Restaurants-1-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/02/1a/60/3a/our-afternoon-tea.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Charming tearoom set in a converted bungalow offering lunch fare  sweets, such as scones  cookies.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/KJ's%20Steakhouse?-FortMyers-Restaurants-2-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1a/ad/5d/4a/32-oz-tomahawk.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A modern flare steakhouse  seafood restaurant, with 2 private dining rooms available for parties or large groups. Vegetarian and Vegan Friendly!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Mina's%20Bistro?-FortMyers-Restaurants-3-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/07/07/31/52/chilean-sea-bass.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We are a family owned and operated restaurant who prides itself in using the best products out there to create the most delicious food in town!!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Downtown%20House%20of%20Pizza?-FortMyers-Restaurants-4-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/16/63/d9/9a/two-massive-pizza-ovens.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Locally owned neighborhood pizzeria in Downtown Fort Myers, making New York style pizza from hand-tossed dough. Watch our pizza makers in our big front window. We offer a full menu of specialty pizzas, slices, calzones, strombolis, hot  cold subs, salads and desserts. Find eight different taps with local craft beers, plus popular domestic and imported beer. Come in for a slice and a local draft beer, enjoy our new dining area or sit by the window and watch the lively downtown neighborhood go by. Limited delivery available. Open: Sunday-Tuesday 10:00am-10:00pm Wednesday-Saturday 10:00am-3:00am Downtown House of Pizza 1520 Hendry Street Downtown Fort Myers, FL 239-337- 3467 (DHOP)</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Oasis%20Restaurant?-FortMyers-Restaurants-5-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/19/de/cd/f6/my-tasty-fresh-crisp.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Established American restaurant features casual meals in a simple venue, plus a pet-friendly patio.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/The%20Veranda?-FortMyers-Restaurants-6-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/18/eb/1a/53/the-veranda-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Nestled in the heart of historic downtown Fort Myers. The Veranda will take you away from the hustle  bustle of everyday life to a bygone era of Antebellum charm. The Veranda's romantic setting in two turn-of-the-century homes, combined with our Southern Regional Cuisine, an extensive wine list, and first class service staff will provide you with the most unique dining experience in Southwest Florida. Celebrating our 35th year in business, The Veranda is consistently honored as one of the most award-winning restaurants in the area. Join us and experience the romance, the history and the charm that is The Veranda!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/McGregor%20Cafe?-FortMyers-Restaurants-7-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0e/32/22/e8/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>McGregor Cafe is one of Ft. Myers’ favorite restaurants, offering fresh, scratch made items for breakfast and lunch. Situated along historic McGregor Blvd., our Cafe is a destination for locals and travelers alike. McGregor Cafe has earned a reputation for consistent, quality food, in a friendly and relaxing atmosphere.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Farmers%20Market%20Restaurant?-FortMyers-Restaurants-8-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/07/21/a2/c8/farmers-market-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Southern food served fresh daily for breakfast and lunch. The oldest restaurant in Lee County, since 1952! Come see us soon!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Izzy's%20Fish%20and%20Oyster?-FortMyers-Restaurants-10-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/24/67/f0/ce/dessert-bread-pudding.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>The concept of Izzy’s Fish  Oyster began with memories of growing up on the shores of Cape Cod and the Islands where summers were filled with sunny days, balmy nights, sandy toes and bellies filled with the freshest seafood New England has to offer. For some, it will be a reminder of similar summertime memories and, for others, a first glance into New England cuisine right here in Ft. Myers. The driving passion is to create a memorable local seafood  beverage dining experience, serving traditional New England fare in a cool, fresh and hip setting. We can’t wait to share our story with you…</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Capone's%20Coal%20Fired%20Pizza?-FortMyers-Restaurants-11-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/06/21/e6/7a/capone-s-at-night.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Welcome to Capone's Coal Fired Pizza, legit since 2014. From the moment you walk through the door you are back in the roaring 20s, with a prohibition bar feel. From the hostesses in flapper dresses to the décor and Al Capone's safe in the basement in the middle of the dining room ... We serve a great thin crust, coal-oven fired pizza, with the freshest custom toppings. Beyond that we are famous for our oven roasted wings and our pasta that is made in house fresh daily. Add a handmade old-school cocktail or a glass of wine from the bar, sit back, relax and enjoy the atmosphere. And your pizza. As we like to say: "Pizza so good, it should be illegal!"</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Ford's%20Garage?-FortMyers-Restaurants-12-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/03/0c/5c/26/ford-s-garage.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Ford's Garage Ft Myers is your top pit stop for the most delicious prime burgers, comfort food and delectable deserts. Conveniently located on First Street just between the Cleveland Ave Bridge and Edison Bridge.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Cabos%20Cantina%20Taco%20%20Tequila%20Bar?-FortMyers-Restaurants-13-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/19/a7/ac/df/front-patio.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Since 2012 Cabos has been serving up some of the best margaritas and Mexican food that you will find in South Florida. Now for our 5-year anniversary we have raised the bar and build a brand new menu around our brand new kitchen: A modern Mexican Scratch Kitchen. Pair this with our highly acclaimed craft margaritas, made with nothing but 100% blue agave tequila and homemade fresh limeade. Welcome to Cabos Cantina - Taco  Tequila Bar.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Kings%20Kitchen%20and%20Bar?-FortMyers-Restaurants-16-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0b/85/3b/c4/kings-kitchen.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Gourmet comfort food with Latin Flair. We have live music outside every night open and for Sunday Brunch. We have a private dining room for events and special occasions.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Sasse's?-FortMyers-Restaurants-17-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-m/1280/1b/d2/01/60/exquisite-masterpieces.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Sasse’s was reopened in October 2012 by Chef Josef Zimmermann. The Restaurant is known for its northern Italian and Mediterranean cuisine and service. The inspiration for Chef Josef is always quality, not quantity, and focused on two words, quality product and execution. Located in the heart of Fort Myers, Sasse’s is a casual cozy restaurant that features authentic Northern-Italian and European food, prepared to perfection in our wood-burning oven.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/The%20Lodge?-FortMyers-Restaurants-18-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0b/19/09/24/dining-room.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Welcome to The Lodge - let the adventure begin! We have a extensive menu, including home-cooked, slow-smoked Southern BBQ. We also feature SW Florida's first  innovative 'self-tap' beer wall, featuring local microbrews. Not to forget about our 15' (~180"!) LED TV for the big game, and our 50' panoramic projection wall with mountain scenes. All of this merged into a historic Downtown Building, with a unique look and feel that will make you feel right at home. Hang out by our 14' tall fireplace and watch the ski-lift run up and down the 'mountain'. And don't forget to say 'hi' to Bert the Grizzly ... see you at The Lodge!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Texas%20Roadhouse?-FortMyers-Restaurants-19-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/03/dc/07/2f/bone-in-rib-eye-with.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Texas Roadhouse is famous for our Hand-Cut Steaks, Fall-Off-The-Bone Ribs, Made-From-Scratch Sides and Dressings, Fresh Baked Bread, Ice Cold Beer, and Legendary Margaritas!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Cristof’s%20on%20McGregor?-FortMyers-Restaurants-20-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0a/d2/9b/29/hamburger-is-great.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Opened mid-October by a locally-known restaurateur, Cristof Danzi</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/La%20Trattoria%20Cafe%20Napoli?-FortMyers-Restaurants-21-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0d/d3/cb/ec/try-this-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We are a family style restaurant featuring Spanish  Italian Cuisine. We have been in business for 15 years with the same outstanding chef since year 1! We have a great local and North East/Midwest US based customer base--please join us for lunch or dinner. Musician on Friday evenings to return soon! Thank you for your support---Go out, but stay safe!!! :-)</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/India’s%20Grill?-FortMyers-Restaurants-23-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/0b/ac/10/73/roasted-veggies.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Indias Grill Fortmyers opened in 2016,we are the authentic Indian restaurant and serving traditional indian recipes using authentic and traditional indian spices and ingredients. we are open 7 days a week and serving lunch and dinner.give us a chance to serve you,welcome to INDIAS GRILL fort myers. Chef Suman</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Famous%20Dave's%20Bar-B-Que?-FortMyers-Restaurants-24-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/0f/57/bc/49/nice.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>One of "Famous" Dave's award-winning BBQ restaurants. Located 1/2 mile north of the Belltower Shops and 1/2 mile south of Page field on US 41. Join us for house-smoked meats, burgers, and sandwiches, and much more! Sit down and dine in, order to go, or have us cater your event!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Pinchers?-FortMyers-Restaurants-25-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0d/69/46/5d/photo3jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Fresh is everything to a seafood restaurant, especially ours, and we try our best to deliver fresh seafood to your table each and every visit. Local fishermen and crabbers leave our shores daily and guide their boats out into the Gulf of Mexico to fish on behalf of Pinchers. They return each night with the best that the Gulf has to offer. They bring this precious catch to us and are one of the primary reasons for our success. In 2007, we purchased the Island Crab Company on Pine Island to serve as a fresh seafood facility for our restaurants. By having our own local facility, we can deliver fresh fish and shellfish to the table faster and fresher - whether its Grouper, Blue Crab, Stone Crab or some of the wonderful fish that you'll see highlighted as specials of the day. Local Fisherman fish Local Waters for a Local Restaurant. You can't get a more Southwest Florida experience than that! Pinchers - Florida Seafood, Florida Style. 13 Locations throughout SW Florida!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Kebab%20Village?-FortMyers-Restaurants-26-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0e/38/3f/00/ta-img-20170121-130807.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Kabab Village Chargrilled Kabab Vegan Vegetarian Open kitchen Late Large Seating in and outdoors! Hookah lounge outdoors with Great atmosphere Middle Eastern Big water Fountain , you will love it . Ahlan wasahlan Shukran</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/The%20Firestone%20Grill%20Room,%20Martini%20Bar%20%20Skybar?-FortMyers-Restaurants-27-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0e/05/a4/94/the-firestone-grill.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Enjoy Masterful Flavor Sensations prepared by Executive Chef James Pryor in our Unique Historic Waterfront Dining Room. The Firestone Grill Room proudly serves the best prime steaks, fresh seafood, fresh local produce, delectable sides and sauces.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Miller's%20Ale%20House%20-%20Ft%20Myers?-FortMyers-Restaurants-28-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0e/69/4a/9d/photo5jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Miller's Ale House is a local restaurant and sports bar where you can eat, drink, watch sports, and enjoy the company of others without breaking the bank.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/The%20Standard?-FortMyers-Restaurants-29-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0f/5f/4e/8f/heavenly-bbq-wings.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>With over fifty years combined experience in the food industry, brothers Chris and Doug Blauvelt introduce their latest culinary venture. Located in the heart of Downtown Ft. Myers, The Standard serves fresh home-cooked style dishes from our "made from scratch" kitchen. Our Executive Chef, Katlyn Johnson, brings her years of experience as well as her wonderful palate for strong, contrasting flavors to every dish served up to our guests. The Standard also serves amazing handcrafted cocktails created by Dawn Barbour and has an impressive wine and beer selection that is sure to satisfy even the most finicky of palates. In addition to legendary food, drinks, and hospitality, The Standard has an incredibly relaxed atmosphere. The combination of iron beams, old brick walls, and thick wooden table tops add to the restaurant's ultra-modern feel. The Standard is open 7 Days a week for Lunch and Dinner and features Saturday and Sunday brunch with bottomless mimosas. Guests have the choice of dining inside or out, and can call ahead or book reservations online. If an amazing all-around dining experience is what you seek, then look no further than "The Standard." No gimmicks, no themes, just great food and good times.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Nauti%20Parrot%20Tiki%20Hut?-FortMyers-Restaurants-32-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/09/9d/5d/2a/nauti-parrot.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Nauti Parrot Tiki Hut features several amenities, combined with an emphasis on value that makes dining with us a unique experience... Waterside Dining Live Music Daily 19 TV's (Inside and Outside) Inside and Outside Bar Raw Seafood Bar Lunch and Dinner Options 14 Foot "Big A** Fan" Live Blue and Gold Macaw Happy Hour From 11-4 Super Happy Hour "2 for 1's" from 4-6 Games for Adults and Children</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Whiskey%20Creek%20Station?-FortMyers-Restaurants-33-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/24/c0/76/db/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We are a local neighborhood restaurant serving your favorite selections of steaks and seafood for dinner, delicious sandwiches and salads for lunch ! . We will also be adding breakfast soon . So come join us in our historical building for good food , handcrafted drinks in a great atmosphere . Patio seating available and take out orders welcome !</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Bullig%20Coffee%20and%20Bites?-FortMyers-Restaurants-34-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/13/ae/81/13/refreshing-peach-raspberry.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>At Bullig, we strive to fuel the goal of making each day count by mixing our love of family, the aroma of good coffee, and tasty bites to satisfy any hunger. Try our iced hunny latte, our wafflewich "Schöllchen" with melted cheese, fresh Roastbeef, bullig made Horseradish and au jus, our "who pooped the waffle" bubble waffle with fresh strawberries and chocolate spread and our awesome Salads aso</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Iguana%20Mia%20of%20Fort%20Myers?-FortMyers-Restaurants-35-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/10/21/5d/cc/located-at-4329-s-cleveland.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Iguana Mia Mexican Restaurant serving great Mexican food and Margaritas to Southwest Florida since 1990! Sorry - we no longer use DoorDash</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/BurgerQuE?-FortMyers-Restaurants-36-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/05/5e/56/68/from-the-back-looking.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>BurgerQuE offers great burgers and bbq. Unique Burger/BBQ combinations are our specialty. We also have an amazing beer selection, including many craft and local craft beers.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Schnitzel%20Express%20Florida?-FortMyers-Restaurants-37-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1a/53/73/d7/we-are-a-rolling-restaurant.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Schnitzel express is a rolling restaurant where guests can select from a Schnitzel selection and daily different specials. When guests order in advance we try to fulfill every single order like in a restaurant. The food trailer is not just a fast food trailer, it is equipped as full functioning restaurant. The portions are large, the quality is only fresh food and the prices are moderate. Also serving communities and events.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Bangkok%20Thai%20Restaurant?-FortMyers-Restaurants-38-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/13/7f/0f/18/we-are-bangkok-proudly.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Bangkok Thai Restaurant is centrally located in the heart of Fort Myers, Florida. We proudly serve traditional and modern Thai cuisine, since 2017.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/First%20Watch?-FortMyers-Restaurants-41-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/03/d4/3c/91/first-watch.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>First Watch specializes in delicious creations freshly-prepared to order. Their fresh, award-winning Breakfast, Brunch and Lunch dishes are made using only the best ingredients without the use of heat lamps or deep fryers. The best part is their creative menu features traditional favorites like omelets, pancakes, salads and sandwiches.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/The%20Mix%20Italian%20Grill?-FortMyers-Restaurants-42-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0f/54/a7/d6/linguini-vongole.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We are committed to bringing our guests a meal they remember. All our dishes are prepared fresh and made from scratch using family recipes and quality ingredients. We don't like shortcuts or "fast food" - we hope you'll join us for a meal and that we can make it one to remember us by!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/European%20American%20Bakery%20Cafe?-FortMyers-Restaurants-45-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/13/81/1f/ab/crushed-avocado-toast.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>European American Bakery Cafe on Metro Pkwy.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Anchor%20In%20Bar%20and%20Grill?-FortMyers-Restaurants-49-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/12/12/44/f2/customers-relaxing-on.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Thank you for your continued support! Now open in Marinatown North Fort Myers, FL...serving hearty sandwiches, homemade pizzas, soups, sauces and desserts! We have 10 large screen TV’s with Direct TV Sports Package and live entertainment! Come visit our outdoor patio on the water...check out our patio furniture with fire pits...so comfy!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/McGregor%20Pizza%20%20Deli%20Co?-FortMyers-Restaurants-50-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/11/41/c9/ff/2-black-olives.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>McGregor Pizza and Deli is locally owned and operated by Katie Madden Marciano, a Fort Myers native who grew up right down the street at Hibiscus Drive. As a child, Katie loved riding her bike to what was once called, "Little Farmers Market" for some candy. In addition to Florida, Katie has also lived in New York, the U.S. Virgin Islands, and Israel and has been working in the food and beverage industry for most of her adult life. She owned and operated a very successful pizzeria in Fort Myers, but has always dreamed of owning her own little spot off of McGregor. McGregor Pizza and Deli is a neighborhood-friendly environment with indoor and outdoor dining, and also offers takeout and delivery. Stop in and see Katie and have a slice!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/City%20Tavern?-FortMyers-Restaurants-51-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/18/cb/b6/d5/city-tavern-ft-myers.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>City Tavern has been a downtown Ft. Myers happy hour and nightlife hot spot since 1998. City Tavern offers a unique bar food menu inspired by Chef Brian Duffy. You will always find the friendliest staff and guests at City. It's where friends meet! Happy Hour daily 4pm-7pm. Cheers!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/10%20Twenty%20Five%20Downtown%20Fort%20Myers?-FortMyers-Restaurants-52-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1a/65/22/15/10-twenty-five.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>10 Twenty Five is family owned  operated in Downtown Fort Myers, FL. We offer scratch kitchen style pub food, crafted cocktails, craft beer and wine. Follow our Instagram @FM10twentyfive</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Joe's%20Crab%20Shack?-FortMyers-Restaurants-53-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/19/08/3b/70/steampot-ii.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Joe's Crab Shack offers a variety of favorites from all parts of the sea and shore. From its extensive menu, guests can choose from buckets of seasonal seafood, fried shrimp platters and fish dishes, as well as options from the "mainland" that include steak, sandwiches, and chicken. Guests can indulge in over-sized and creative cocktails, such as the Shark Bite which is playfully garnished with a shark toy. Since its inception, Joe's popularity has stemmed not only from its menu, but also its retail store. With various pieces of merchandise for purchase, including the ever-popular tie-dye T-shirt with the phrase "Peace, Love and Crabs," Joe's has become synonymous with the word "fun."</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Twisted%20Vine%20Bistro?-FortMyers-Restaurants-56-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/05/bd/b7/d4/twisted-vine-bistro.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Twisted Vine Bistro, located in downtown Fort Myers' historic river district, prides itself in an extraordinary dining experience. We are a beautiful polished, casual upscale restaurant that has an eclectic menu, a full liquor bar, and a wonderful boutique wine list. We offer only the freshest seafood, certified Angus Beef, and other local unique innovative entrees. We also feature an extensive wine list, with over thirty wines by the glass. We even grow our own house herbs and spices in our courtyard garden, which is available for private parties and events, and have partnered with Roots Hertitage Urban Food Hub, a non-profit organization locally growing our in-season produce, to source local ingredients as much as possible. As if the food wasn't enough, we like to have fun and provide live entertainment on the weekends, are big supporters of the Florida Reparatory Theatre, Sidney and Berne Davis Art Center and host networking events during the week to help connect the community.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Lan%20Xang%20Fort%20Myers?-FortMyers-Restaurants-62-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/22/1f/46/dc/drunken-noodle-seafood.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>"Lan Xang offers authentic Asian cuisine including Laos, Thai, and Vietnamese food as well as dim sum and boba. Join us for lunch or dinner Tuesday through Sunday. Dine in, take out or order delivery."</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Siam%20Thai%20and%20Sushi?-FortMyers-Restaurants-63-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/07/c8/fd/f4/siam-thai-and-sushi.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We are a small, family run Thai and sushi restaurant serving North Fort Myers for over 7 years.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Monarca's%20Authentic%20Mexican%20Cuisine%20Bar%20%20Grill?-FortMyers-Restaurants-66-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/16/44/46/fe/monarca-s-fort-myers.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Monarca’s restaurant is inspired by our family history. We pay homage to the diversity and cultural richness, providing our family touch. Come and enjoy in Monarcas with a large family room with capacity for 270 people and a cozy bar. Monarca stands out for being the number one restaurant in the area because our dishes, service and pleasant place. Visit us today and feel like you were in Mexico. You will enjoy fresh and delicious dishes such as fajitas, molcajete, tacos, enchiladas, chimichanga, ceviche. Also prepare to enjoy delicious margaritas, cocktails and michelada drinks.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Chef%20Brooke's%20Natural%20Cafe?-FortMyers-Restaurants-67-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/06/b8/75/48/chef-brooke-s-natural.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Come in, Relax, enjoy the music. All food is Organic and Home-made with Love. Best House coffee and tea, Bakery, Superfood Smoothies and Juicebar, Wheatgrass, COOKING CLASSES, Spectacular Lunch. Gluten-Free Friendly</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Habaneros%20Mexican%20Grill?-FortMyers-Restaurants-69-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/21/d6/b5/74/our-logo-we-are-located.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Habaneros Mexican Grill is a Mexican Restaurant located in North Fort Myers, FL. We do not only specialize in Authentic Mexican Food but we also provide high-quality customer service to each one of our customers. Here we love to make you feel welcome.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Sabor%20A%20Mexico?-FortMyers-Restaurants-71-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/1b/d1/a6/bf/shrimp-never-tasted-so.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Here at Sabor A Mexico in Fort Myers, we make our day about the food as well as the customer, providing excellence in service and taste. Our authentic Mexican menu is freshly prepared with braised, grilled, or fried meats and vegetables, the toppings of your choice, the finest ingredients, signature sauces, delicious sides, and the best-tasting tortillas. We are serving refreshing authentic drinks  cocktails all day.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Living%20Vine%20Organic%20Cafe?-FortMyers-Restaurants-73-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/21/22/1e/da/indoor-dining-room.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Fresh  Organic Raw Juices, Wheatgrass, Smoothies, Shakes, Açaí  Pitaya Bowls, Coffee drinks, Teas, Homemade drinks, Kombucha  Kefir. Vegan  Gluten Free Baked Goods. Plant-Based, Vegetarian, Meat  Gluten Free Food Options. Dine-In with Outdoor Seating or Carry-Out. All fresh, locally sourced, organic, natural, healthy, non GMO ingredients. Amazing daily specials... Family owned and operated organic cafe</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Fowler%20Street%20Grill?-FortMyers-Restaurants-74-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/03/a3/0a/03/what-a-breakfast-a-small.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We've been serving Fort Myers and all of Lee County great food at reasonable prices since 1987! Conveniently located on the corner of Fowler and Carrell, come enjoy breakfast from open til close or any of our fantastic, filling entr</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/De%20Adriatico?-FortMyers-Restaurants-77-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/24/8a/11/f9/caption.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>De Adriatico Restaurant it’s a European inspired, family owned restaurant. It brings a Mediterranean flair highlighting Italian, Serbian, and Greek dishes. Few of the owner’s favorites include, braised lamb shank, baked octopus, baked eggplant, and grilled scampi. De Adriatico Restaurant opens at 4pm to 10pm Tuesday through Sunday.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Catch%2022%20Live%20Music%20%20Sports%20Bar?-FortMyers-Restaurants-78-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/05/6c/6a/dc/catch-22.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Live Music and Sports Bar. Laid Back Atmosphere! Awesome Food! Best Live Entertainment! Prop Karaoke! BuzzTime, Pool, Darts, Live Poker Saturdays 7pm</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Ella%20Mae’s%20Diner?-FortMyers-Restaurants-81-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1c/b9/46/cd/ella-mae-s-has-a-retro.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A classic yet modern diner where everyone is welcome. Sit and stay awhile in this neighborhood gathering spot. The hospitality is genuine and the good feelings are mutual. Let the fun vibe and sleek decor evoke a simpler past. Reminisce over traditional dishes, prepared with a lighter touch. It’s soul food with finesse.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Perkins%20Restaurant%20%20Bakery?-FortMyers-Restaurants-82-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0a/71/3e/fa/perkins-restaurant-bakery.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Since it was founded in 1958 as a single pancake house in Ohio, Perkins today has nearly 300 restaurants in 32 states and Canada, of which approximately 85 are company-owned. Committed to delivering 100% satisfaction through service excellence and positive dining experiences, the brand embraces a "Kindness Served Daily" philosophy.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Herons%20Glen%20Golf%20%20Country%20Club?-FortMyers-Restaurants-84-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/03/7c/bb/77/heron-s-glen.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Part of an Adult Community Country Club with the same name</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Smallcakes%20Cupcakery%20and%20Creamery-Fort%20Myers?-FortMyers-Restaurants-87-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/15/30/2d/99/20181028-222314-0-largejpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Smallcakes Fort Myers offers Gourmet cupcakes baked fresh daily! Custom Cake, Custom Cookies and more!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Cafe%20Brazil%20Restaurant?-FortMyers-Restaurants-89-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/07/c7/02/7c/shrimp-stew.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Located at the corner of 3940 Metro Parkway and Winkler Avenue, suites 111/112. BEST BRAZILIAN FOOD SWFL! TripAdvisor</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Skyline%20Chili?-FortMyers-Restaurants-90-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/06/a3/55/a5/skyline-chili.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Skyline Chili restaurant chain. Famous for secret recipe Cincinnati-style chili  fast, friendly dine-in  drive-thru service. Serving Cheese Coneys, Ways, Greek Salad  more great-tasting food since 1949. Locations in OH, NKY, IN  FL. Grocery products available in OH, KY, IN  Chicago.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Wicked%20Good%20Deli?-FortMyers-Restaurants-92-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/0e/48/03/6d/enter.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>New locally owned and operated deli in Fort Myers. We have everything from the traditional Philly sub to custom made sandwiches. We also have hand cut fries, rice bowls, salads, and much more. Stop in today and like our Facebook for more info and offers!</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Ceviches%20By%20Divino%20Fort%20Myers%20-%20Peruvian%20Tapas%20%20Gastrobar?-FortMyers-Restaurants-93-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/24/8b/1a/74/causa-crocante-de-tuna.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Ceviches by Divino is a Gastropub with an industrial ambiance. Our distinct menu has been carefully prepared to highlight the authentic flavors of our homeland cuisine by properly presenting high level Peruvian Tapas, Rolls, Pokes as well as Ceviche’s. In addition a broad variety of the most popular craft beers and exceptional cocktails are available to pair with lunch or dinner perfectly. Strategically located in Dani Drive, Fort Myers. Ceviches by Divino offers genuine Peruvian flavors in a relaxed atmosphere ideal to chill with friends and family.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Red%20Lobster?-FortMyers-Restaurants-94-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/01/c4/df/f0/fancy-dessert-at-red.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Red Lobster is known as the foremost expert in fresh seafood. Our commitment to serving quality seafood starts long before you sit down at our restaurant. Fresh Fish, Live Lobster.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/H%20J%20German%20Corner?-FortMyers-Restaurants-97-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-o/22/65/62/23/jagerschnitzel-a-slice.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Authentic German Food, Beer  Wine. Chef Hans Joachim moved to Florida in 2007 working hard to learn the language as he worked for several other restaurants and eateries. In 2012 he opened the Bavarian Haus Restaurant in Mount Dora Fl., and with its success Chef Hans has brought his love for German food and Florida salt air to the Fort Myers area. We refuse to compromise on quality in our restaurant, and look forward to serving you.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Crazy%20Dingo%20Brewing%20Company?-FortMyers-Restaurants-98-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/21/cd/56/c3/the-brewery.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Family friendly, small-batch brew pub creating delicious ales with a South Florida twist. Located at Southern Fresh Farms in Fort Myers FL.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Cactus%20Jacks%20Waterfront%20Bar%20%20Grill?-FortMyers-Restaurants-99-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/04/2d/c4/73/it-looked-super-cute.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Cactus Jack's Waterfront Bar  Grill provides Starters, Salads, Entrees, Desserts and Lunch Menu to the North Fort Myers, FL area.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Oxbow%20Bar%20%20Grill?-FortMyers-Restaurants-100-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1c/d3/cc/31/oxbow-bar-grill-located.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Casual dockside dining on the doorstep of Downtown Fort Myers. Panoramic riverfront views on the Caloosahatchee. A boater’s retreat with an upbeat nautical vibe. Serving coastal cuisine and more for brunch, lunch and dinner. Retail and rentals to ignite your spirit of adventure.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Tony's%20NY%20Pizza?-FortMyers-Restaurants-105-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-p/19/69/28/9e/photo0jpg.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>New York Style Pizzeria</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Beacon%20Social%20Drinkery?-FortMyers-Restaurants-106-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1c/6e/b8/63/west-patio-at-beacon.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>A sophisticated rooftop gathering that beckons. Lively elixirs to savor. Inventive noshes to satisfy. The spirited atmosphere elicits stories of old and draws friendships anew. Twelve floors below, the river’s gentle current shimmers. Scan the horizon and watch another day of possibilities emerge.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Edison%20Lunch%20Box?-FortMyers-Restaurants-110-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/07/17/a9/cd/edison-lunch-box.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We provide quality meals, specials, sandwiches and desserts to the customers at the Lee County Justice Center. Edison Lunch box will be proudly partnering with LARC and Lee County to provide job training skills to our special populations group.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Bob%20Evans?-FortMyers-Restaurants-111-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/0f/e1/02/c0/bacon-burger.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>Welcome to the home of America's Farm Fresh! Enjoy our all-day menu featuring signature breakfasts, NEW Banana Nut Hotcakes and homestyle Family Meals to Go at your Bob Evans in Fort Meyers. Order online for curbside pickup or delivery (where available). Download the farm!🚜 Ordering your homestyle favorites from Bob Evans has gotten easier than ever before. Save your favorite orders, pay using your phone when you dine-in, get exclusive offers and more with Bob Evans mobile app.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Maverick%20Grille?-FortMyers-Restaurants-112-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-s/1b/66/82/8f/stak-with-tziki-and-5.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We build it your way, serving delicious food fast, customized just the way you want it. Every dish is made fresh with only the very best ingredients. We take pride in helping you make healthier choices, so you can enjoy dining with us much more often. We give back to the community. Serving lunch and dinner daily at all locations in Southwest Florida, Maverick Grille has something for everyone.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

<url>

<loc>https://www.thingsflorida.com/things/FortMyers/Chicago%20Boys%20Bar%20%20Grill?-FortMyers-Restaurants-120-</loc>

<lastmod>2023-01-07T15:12:35+00:00</lastmod>

<changefreq>monthly</changefreq>

<priority>0.7</priority>

<image:image>

<image:loc>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-w/1a/8d/bd/84/chicago-boys-bar-and.jpg</image:loc>

<image:title>We are dedicated to serving excellence to people who want simple, delicious cuisine. We strive to give our customers the best culinary experience possible. Using only the freshest ingredients and serving them in a warm, comfortable atmosphere, each meal spent in the company of our friendly staff will always be a pleasurable experience. We are also devoted to making sure you don't go home hungry.</image:title>

</image:image>

</url>

</urlset>